1
00:00:07,173 --> 00:00:09,175
HELP !
[ Grunts ]

2
00:00:11,177 --> 00:00:13,680
HELP !

3
00:00:13,680 --> 00:00:16,182
SOMEBODY HELP ME !

4
00:00:18,568 --> 00:00:20,954
HELP !

5
00:00:20,954 --> 00:00:22,789
[ Panting ]

6
00:00:24,240 --> 00:00:27,660
OH, HE'S GONNA KILL ME !

7
00:00:29,512 --> 00:00:33,099
HELP !
GOD, SOMEBODY HELP ME !

8
00:00:34,401 --> 00:00:36,436
GO AWAY !
[ Screams ]

9
00:00:36,436 --> 00:00:39,005
HELP !
[ Screams ]

10
00:00:39,005 --> 00:00:41,674
[ Panting ]

11
00:00:44,027 --> 00:00:46,529
PLEASE HELP ME !

12
00:00:49,032 --> 00:00:51,251
[ Grunts ]

13
00:00:51,251 --> 00:00:54,888
[ Grunting ]
HELP !

14
00:01:04,781 --> 00:01:07,901
MULDER ?

15
00:01:22,182 --> 00:01:24,100
LOOK AT THAT.

16
00:01:27,937 --> 00:01:30,440
HUH ?  HUH ?

17
00:01:43,269 --> 00:01:45,271
OH, SHI--

18
00:02:29,515 --> 00:02:31,517
[ Door Closes ]

19
00:02:31,517 --> 00:02:35,020
[ Tapping Pen
  Rhythmically ]

20
00:02:43,512 --> 00:02:45,297
MULDER--
DON'T.

21
00:02:46,682 --> 00:02:48,968
DON'T EVEN START WITH ME.

22
00:03:05,885 --> 00:03:08,837
I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
[ Sighs ]

23
00:03:14,126 --> 00:03:17,980
SKINNER WANTS A REPORT
IN ONE HOUR.

24
00:03:17,980 --> 00:03:20,482
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL HIM ?

25
00:03:20,482 --> 00:03:23,235
I'M GONNA TELL HIM
EXACTLY WHAT I SAW.

26
00:03:24,570 --> 00:03:26,372
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA TELL HIM ?

27
00:03:26,372 --> 00:03:29,258
I'LL TELL HIM
EXACTLY WHAT I SAW.

28
00:03:29,258 --> 00:03:32,211
NOW, HOW IS THAT DIFFERENT ?

29
00:03:32,711 --> 00:03:35,364
I'M THE ONE WHO MAY WIND UP
GOING TO PRISON HERE.

30
00:03:35,364 --> 00:03:37,233
I GOTTA KNOW
IF YOU'RE GONNA BACK ME UP.

31
00:03:38,701 --> 00:03:40,703
FIRST OF ALL,

32
00:03:40,703 --> 00:03:44,206
IF THE FAMILY OF RONNIE
STRICKLAND DOES, INDEED,
DECIDE TO SUE THE F.B.I...

33
00:03:44,206 --> 00:03:47,459
FOR-- I THINK THE FIGURE
IS $446 MILLION--

34
00:03:47,459 --> 00:03:51,213
THEN YOU AND I BOTH
WILL MOST CERTAINLY
BE CODEFENDANTS.

35
00:03:51,213 --> 00:03:55,718
AND SECOND OF ALL--
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
A SECOND OF ALL, MULDER.

36
00:03:56,218 --> 00:03:59,104
FOUR HUNDRED AND FORTY-SIX
MILLION DOLLARS.

37
00:03:59,104 --> 00:04:02,925
I'M IN THIS AS DEEP AS YOU ARE,
AND I'M NOT EVEN THE ONE
THAT OVERREACTED.

38
00:04:02,925 --> 00:04:05,527
I DIDN'T DO THE--
WITH THE THING.
I DID NOT OVERREACT.

39
00:04:05,527 --> 00:04:08,047
RONNIE STRICKLAND
WAS A VAMPIRE.
WHERE'S YOUR PROOF ?

40
00:04:08,047 --> 00:04:10,549
YOU'RE MY PROOF.
YOU WERE THERE.

41
00:04:10,549 --> 00:04:13,369
NOW YOU'RE SCARING ME.
I WANT TO HEAR WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA TELL SKINNER.

42
00:04:13,369 --> 00:04:15,704
YOU WANT OUR STORIES
STRAIGHT.
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.

43
00:04:15,704 --> 00:04:18,357
I JUST WANT TO HEAR IT
THE WAY YOU SAW IT.

44
00:04:18,357 --> 00:04:20,426
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH THAT.

45
00:04:20,426 --> 00:04:23,796
PRISON, SCULLY.
YOUR CELL MATE'S NICKNAME
IS GONNA BE "LARGE MARGE."

46
00:04:23,796 --> 00:04:26,181
SHE'S GONNA READ
A LOT OF GERTRUDE STEIN.

47
00:04:28,617 --> 00:04:32,037
- ALL RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT, START
  AT THE BEGINNING.

48
00:04:33,405 --> 00:04:35,190
THE VERY BEGINNING ?

49
00:04:37,059 --> 00:04:38,944
[ Drawer Opens ]

50
00:04:38,944 --> 00:04:40,946
FINE.

51
00:04:42,781 --> 00:04:44,917
[ Sighs ]

52
00:04:44,917 --> 00:04:48,370
YESTERDAY MORNING...

53
00:04:48,370 --> 00:04:50,873
WHEN I ARRIVED AT WORK,

54
00:04:50,873 --> 00:04:55,711
YOU WERE, UH...
CHARACTERISTICALLY EXUBERANT.

55
00:04:55,711 --> 00:05:00,165
HOPE YOU BROUGHT
YOUR COWBOY BOOTS !
YOU WANT US TO GO TO DALLAS ?

56
00:05:00,165 --> 00:05:03,552
YEE-HAW !  ACTUALLY
A TOWN CALLED CHENEY ABOUT
50 MILES SOUTH OF THERE.

57
00:05:04,053 --> 00:05:06,805
POPULATION: 361.
BY ALL ACCOUNTS,
VERY RUSTIC AND CHARMING.

58
00:05:06,805 --> 00:05:08,957
BUT AS OF LATE,
GROUND ZERO, THE LOCUS...

59
00:05:08,957 --> 00:05:11,276
FOR A SERIES OF MYSTERIOUS
NOCTURNAL EXSANGUINATIONS.

60
00:05:11,276 --> 00:05:13,479
EXSANGUINATIONS.
OF WHOM ?

61
00:05:13,479 --> 00:05:16,265
[ Slides Clicking Into Place ]
[ Mulder ]
HOW DOES THAT GRAB YA ?

62
00:05:18,167 --> 00:05:20,436
- IT'S A--
- DEAD COW !  EXACTLY.

63
00:05:20,436 --> 00:05:22,621
OR MORE SPECIFICALLY,
A DEAD 900-POUND HOLSTEIN.

64
00:05:22,621 --> 00:05:25,341
ITS BODY COMPLETELY DRAINED
OF BLOOD, AS WAS THIS ONE,

65
00:05:25,341 --> 00:05:28,260
THIS ONE, THIS ONE,
 THIS ONE, AND SO ON--

66
00:05:28,260 --> 00:05:31,864
SIX, ALL IN ALL--
APPROXIMATELY ONE A WEEK
OVER THE PAST SIX WEEKS.

67
00:05:31,864 --> 00:05:33,849
- ANY SIGN OF--
- TWO SMALL PUNCTURE WOUNDS
  ON THE NECK ?

68
00:05:33,849 --> 00:05:36,802
- NOT WHAT I WAS GONNA ASK.
- TOO BAD.  WE GOT 'EM.
  CHECK IT OUT.

69
00:05:38,704 --> 00:05:42,191
THESE MAY BE SYRINGE MARKS,
THEIR PLACEMENT MEANT
TO EMULATE FANGS.

70
00:05:42,191 --> 00:05:45,194
SUCH RITUALISTIC BLOODLETTING
POINTS TOWARDS CULTISTS
OF SOME SORT,

71
00:05:45,194 --> 00:05:48,997
IN WHICH CASE--
WHAT ?

72
00:05:48,997 --> 00:05:52,768
YEAH, THAT'S PROBABLY IT.
SATANIC CULTISTS.
COME ON, SCULLY.

73
00:05:52,768 --> 00:05:55,170
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL ME THIS
IS THAT MEXICAN GOAT SUCKER.

74
00:05:55,170 --> 00:05:57,623
EL CHUPACABRA ?
 THEY GOT FOUR FANGS, NOT TWO.

75
00:05:57,623 --> 00:06:02,094
- AND THEY SUCK GOATS,
  HENCE THE NAME.
- SO INSTEAD THIS WOULD BE ?

76
00:06:02,094 --> 00:06:05,297
- CLASSIC VAMPIRISM.
- OF A BUNCH OF COWS ?

77
00:06:05,297 --> 00:06:07,716
AND ONE DEAD HUMAN.
LAST NIGHT A VACATIONER
FROM NEW JERSEY.

78
00:06:07,716 --> 00:06:09,935
COME ON.
WE GOTTA GO.

79
00:06:09,935 --> 00:06:11,937
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
THAT FROM THE BEGINNING ?

80
00:06:11,937 --> 00:06:14,440
LOCK THE DOOR
ON YOUR WAY OUT.
[ Disgusted Sigh ]

81
00:06:14,440 --> 00:06:18,844
[ Scully's Voice ]
THE TOWN OF CHENEY IS TOO SMALL
TO MAINTAIN A MORGUE FACILITY.

82
00:06:19,344 --> 00:06:23,849
AS SUCH, WE MADE OUR WAY
TO THE PEACEFUL SLUMBERS
FUNERAL HOME...

83
00:06:23,849 --> 00:06:27,352
IN ORDER TO EXAMINE THE BODY
OF ONE MR. DWIGHT FUNT,

84
00:06:27,352 --> 00:06:29,188
RECENTLY DECEASED.

85
00:06:29,188 --> 00:06:31,507
[ Man Talking
  Quietly ]

86
00:06:32,007 --> 00:06:35,477
[ Scully ]
IT WAS THERE THAT WE WERE MET
BY A REPRESENTATIVE...

87
00:06:35,477 --> 00:06:37,479
OF LOCAL LAW ENFORCEMENT,

88
00:06:37,980 --> 00:06:40,149
SHERIFF--
LUCIUS HARTWELL.

89
00:06:41,884 --> 00:06:45,320
- YOU THE F.B.I. AGENTS ?
- YES.  I'M--

90
00:06:45,320 --> 00:06:47,773
AGENTS MULDER AND, UH--
[ Snapping Fingers ]

91
00:06:47,773 --> 00:06:51,243
SCULLY.  WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR VICTIM ?
YEAH, BY ALL MEANS.

92
00:06:51,243 --> 00:06:53,662
AFTER YOU.

93
00:06:58,100 --> 00:07:01,203
COME ON, SCULLY.
GET THOSE LITTLE LEGS
MOVIN'.  COME ON.

94
00:07:05,007 --> 00:07:07,009
BOY.

95
00:07:08,761 --> 00:07:10,629
HERE WE GO.

96
00:07:12,131 --> 00:07:14,133
NICE THREADS.

97
00:07:15,134 --> 00:07:16,969
NO EXAM HAS BEEN DONE ?

98
00:07:16,969 --> 00:07:20,422
NO, MA'AM.
HE'S JUST LIKE WE FOUND HIM
IN THE MOTEL ROOM.

99
00:07:20,923 --> 00:07:24,793
ONCE I HEARD YOU FOLKS WERE
INTERESTED, I FIGURED WE'D BEST
LEAVE IT UP TO THE EXPERTS.

100
00:07:26,078 --> 00:07:29,448
YOUR SATANIC CULTISTS HAVE
SOME SHARP LITTLE TEETH.

101
00:07:30,682 --> 00:07:32,801
WHAT SATANIC CULTISTS ?

102
00:07:32,801 --> 00:07:34,920
GO AHEAD, TELL HIM
YOUR, UH, "THEORY."

103
00:07:36,505 --> 00:07:40,559
WELL, MY THEORY HAS EVOLVED.

104
00:07:40,559 --> 00:07:44,913
BASICALLY, I THINK WE'RE
LOOKING FOR SOMEONE WHO HAS SEEN
ONE TOO MANY BELA LUGOSI MOVIES.

105
00:07:45,414 --> 00:07:47,916
HE BELIEVES HE IS A VAMPIRE,
THEREFORE HE--

106
00:07:47,916 --> 00:07:50,519
THEY ACT LIKE ONE.
YEAH.  YEAH.

107
00:07:50,519 --> 00:07:52,321
THAT MAKES A WHOLE
LOT OF SENSE.

108
00:07:52,321 --> 00:07:56,275
- I THINK SHE'S RIGHT.
- WHAT ABOUT THE FANG MARKS ?

109
00:07:56,275 --> 00:07:59,862
WELL, SOMEONE SO OBSESSED
MIGHT WELL FILE DOWN
THEIR INCISORS.

110
00:07:59,862 --> 00:08:03,866
I THINK THAT A MOULAGE CASTING
SHOULD HELP US MAKE
AN IDENTIFICATION.

111
00:08:03,866 --> 00:08:07,553
MOULAGE CASTING.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.

112
00:08:08,904 --> 00:08:11,306
NOW--

113
00:08:11,306 --> 00:08:15,811
NOW, ISN'T THERE SOME KIND
OF DISEASE THAT MAKES A PERSON
THINK THAT THEY'RE A VAMPIRE ?

114
00:08:15,811 --> 00:08:19,815
WELL, THERE IS
A PSYCHOLOGICAL FIXATION
CALLED HEMATODIPSIA,

115
00:08:19,815 --> 00:08:23,769
WHICH CAUSES THE SUFFERER
TO GAIN EROTIC SATISFACTION...

116
00:08:23,769 --> 00:08:25,771
FROM CONSUMING
HUMAN BLOOD.

117
00:08:26,271 --> 00:08:29,091
EROTIC.  YEAH.

118
00:08:31,460 --> 00:08:33,779
THERE ARE ALSO GENETIC
AFFLICTIONS...

119
00:08:33,779 --> 00:08:36,148
WHICH CAUSE A HEIGHTENED
SENSITIVITY TO LIGHT,

120
00:08:36,148 --> 00:08:38,150
UH, TO GARLIC.

121
00:08:38,150 --> 00:08:40,619
PORPHYRIA.

122
00:08:40,619 --> 00:08:43,955
XERODERMA PIGMENTOSUM.

123
00:08:45,257 --> 00:08:48,977
YOU REALLY KNOW
YOUR STUFF, DANA.

124
00:08:48,977 --> 00:08:51,330
"DANA" ?

125
00:08:51,330 --> 00:08:54,032
HE NEVER EVEN KNEW
YOUR FIRST NAME.

126
00:08:56,034 --> 00:08:59,705
- YOU GONNA INTERRUPT ME,
  OR WHAT ?
- NO, GO AHEAD.

127
00:09:00,939 --> 00:09:02,741
DANA.

128
00:09:02,741 --> 00:09:05,243
ANYWAY,

129
00:09:05,744 --> 00:09:09,631
THAT'S WHEN YOU HAD
YOUR BIG BREAKTHROUGH--
WHATEVER.

130
00:09:09,631 --> 00:09:13,085
AGENT SCULLY, YOU REALLY
KNOW YOUR STUFF.

131
00:09:13,085 --> 00:09:16,088
SHERIFF, YOU SAY
THIS MAN ISEXACTLY
AS YOU FOUND HIM ?

132
00:09:16,588 --> 00:09:19,591
YES, SIR,
TO THE LETTER.

133
00:09:19,591 --> 00:09:23,645
HAVE YOU NOTICED
THAT THIS MAN'S SHOES
ARE UNTIED ?

134
00:09:23,645 --> 00:09:26,815
- YEAH, THEY SURE ARE.
- MULDER, WHAT'S YOUR POINT ?

135
00:09:26,815 --> 00:09:29,434
THIS MEANS SOMETHING.

136
00:09:29,935 --> 00:09:33,355
DO YOU HAVE AN OLD CEMETERY
IN TOWN, OFF THE BEATEN PATH,
THE CREEPIER THE BETTER ?

137
00:09:34,623 --> 00:09:36,625
UH, YEAH.

138
00:09:36,625 --> 00:09:39,561
- TAKE ME THERE NOW.
- MULDER.

139
00:09:39,561 --> 00:09:42,414
WE'RE GONNA NEED A COMPLETE
AUTOPSY ON THIS MAN,
THE SOONER THE BETTER.

140
00:09:42,414 --> 00:09:45,167
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.

141
00:09:49,087 --> 00:09:51,590
WHAT AM I
EVEN LOOKING FOR ?

142
00:09:53,592 --> 00:09:55,844
I DON'T KNOW.

143
00:10:00,966 --> 00:10:04,770
- HE DOES THAT.
- COME ON, SHERIFF HARTWELL.

144
00:10:08,273 --> 00:10:10,275
MA'AM.

145
00:10:36,802 --> 00:10:39,304
4:54 P.M.

146
00:10:39,304 --> 00:10:43,308
BEGIN AUTOPSY
ON WHITE MALE, AGE 60,

147
00:10:43,308 --> 00:10:47,813
WHO IS ARGUABLY HAVING
A WORSE TIME IN TEXAS
THAN I AM,

148
00:10:47,813 --> 00:10:50,315
ALTHOUGH NOT BY MUCH.

149
00:10:50,315 --> 00:10:52,818
I'LL BEGIN
WITH THE "Y" INCISION.

150
00:10:52,818 --> 00:10:55,821
[ Blade Hits Floor ]

151
00:10:56,321 --> 00:10:57,823
YEE-HAW.

152
00:11:01,827 --> 00:11:05,330
HEART WEIGHS 370 GRAMS.

153
00:11:05,330 --> 00:11:08,333
TISSUE APPEARS HEALTHY.

154
00:11:10,335 --> 00:11:14,623
LEFT LUNG WEIGHS 345 GRAMS.
TISSUE APPEARS HEALTHY.

155
00:11:19,461 --> 00:11:22,464
LARGE INTESTINE,

156
00:11:22,464 --> 00:11:24,466
890 GRAMS.

157
00:11:24,466 --> 00:11:27,052
YADA, YADA, YADA.

158
00:11:33,458 --> 00:11:37,546
STOMACH CONTENTS SHOW LAST MEAL
CLOSE TO THE TIME OF DEATH...

159
00:11:38,547 --> 00:11:41,049
CONSISTING OF...

160
00:11:41,049 --> 00:11:43,051
PIZZA,

161
00:11:43,051 --> 00:11:45,971
TOPPED WITH PEPPERONI,

162
00:11:46,471 --> 00:11:48,473
GREEN PEPPERS,

163
00:11:48,974 --> 00:11:50,475
MUSHROOMS.

164
00:11:51,977 --> 00:11:53,979
MUSHROOMS.

165
00:11:54,980 --> 00:11:57,983
[ Sighs ]
THAT SOUNDS REALLY GOOD.

166
00:11:59,484 --> 00:12:01,786
[ Neck Muscles Cracking ]
[ Sighs ]

167
00:12:01,786 --> 00:12:04,155
[ Scully's Voice ]
HAVING COMPLETED THE AUTOPSY,

168
00:12:04,656 --> 00:12:07,158
I CHECKED INTO THE DAVEY
CROCKETT MOTOR COURT.

169
00:12:07,158 --> 00:12:11,413
[ Mulder ]
THE NAME OF IT WAS ACTUALLY
THE SAM HOUSTON MOTOR LODGE.

170
00:12:15,867 --> 00:12:18,720
[ Bed Motor Humming ]
[ Sighs ]

171
00:12:24,726 --> 00:12:26,478
[ Whispering ]
OH, MY GOD.

172
00:12:26,478 --> 00:12:28,697
[ Door Hinges Creak,
   Door Slams ]

173
00:12:28,697 --> 00:12:30,899
CHLORAL HYDRATE.

174
00:12:30,899 --> 00:12:33,518
WHAT ?

175
00:12:35,370 --> 00:12:39,474
- WHAT THE HELL
  HAPPENED TO YOU ?
- NOTHIN'.

176
00:12:40,475 --> 00:12:42,277
CHLORAL HYDRATE ?

177
00:12:42,277 --> 00:12:45,180
YEAH, THAT THING
THAT YOU DIDN'T KNOW
THAT YOU WERE LOOKING FOR.

178
00:12:45,180 --> 00:12:48,183
CHLORAL HYDRATE,
MORE COLORFULLY KNOWN
AS "KNOCKOUT DROPS."

179
00:12:48,683 --> 00:12:52,938
I FOUND IT IN ABUNDANCE
WHEN I SENT THE TOX SCREEN IN
ON OUR MURDER VICTIM.

180
00:12:52,938 --> 00:12:56,391
- NO, SERIOUSLY, MULDER.
  WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU ?
- NOTHING.

181
00:12:56,391 --> 00:13:00,028
- WHO SLIPPED HIM THE MICKEY ?
- MY "THEORY" ?

182
00:13:00,028 --> 00:13:02,030
YOUR VAMPIRE.

183
00:13:02,030 --> 00:13:04,950
HE FOUND IT NECESSARY
TO DOPE POOR MR. FUNT
TO THE GILLS...

184
00:13:04,950 --> 00:13:07,902
BEFORE HE WAS ABLE
TO EXTRACT HIS BLOOD.

185
00:13:07,902 --> 00:13:10,905
PROBABLY DID IT
TO THE COWS TOO.

186
00:13:10,905 --> 00:13:13,291
WHAT KIND OF VAMPIRE
WOULD DO THAT ?

187
00:13:13,291 --> 00:13:15,193
EXACTLY.

188
00:13:15,193 --> 00:13:19,047
[ Sighs ]

189
00:13:19,047 --> 00:13:21,833
WE GOT ANOTHER DEAD TOURIST.
YOU GOTTA DO ANOTHER AUTOPSY.

190
00:13:21,833 --> 00:13:24,319
TONIGHT ?

191
00:13:25,754 --> 00:13:28,006
I JUST PUT MONEY
IN THE MAGIC FINGERS.

192
00:13:28,006 --> 00:13:30,825
I WON'T LET IT GO TO WASTE.

193
00:13:30,825 --> 00:13:32,661
[ Bed Continues Vibrating ]

194
00:13:33,161 --> 00:13:34,663
[ Sighs ]

195
00:13:40,669 --> 00:13:43,171
[ Giggling ]

196
00:13:43,171 --> 00:13:48,460
[ Giggling Continues ]

197
00:13:48,460 --> 00:13:52,697
THIS ONE'S MY ROOM, MULDER.
DON'T GET MUD EVERYWHERE.

198
00:13:52,697 --> 00:13:55,116
YEAH.  YEAH, YEAH,
 YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.

199
00:13:55,116 --> 00:13:57,419
OKAY.
[ Giggling ]

200
00:14:04,142 --> 00:14:07,145
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
DID YOU ORDER A PIZZA ?

201
00:14:07,145 --> 00:14:10,649
YEAH.  THE GUY IN THERE
WILL PAY FOR IT.

202
00:14:27,431 --> 00:14:30,434
[ Scully's Voice ]
FORGOING BOTH DINNER
AND SLEEP,

203
00:14:30,434 --> 00:14:32,820
I WAS SOON BACK
AT THE FUNERAL HOME...

204
00:14:32,820 --> 00:14:35,322
EXAMINING ONE
MR. PAUL LOMBARDO...

205
00:14:35,322 --> 00:14:38,325
FROM NAPLES, FLORIDA.

206
00:14:39,794 --> 00:14:43,247
HEART.  LUNG.

207
00:14:43,247 --> 00:14:45,016
LARGE INTESTINE.

208
00:14:47,518 --> 00:14:49,353
[ Sighs ]

209
00:14:49,353 --> 00:14:53,641
[ Sighs Deeply ]

210
00:14:54,141 --> 00:14:57,144
AS WITH THE PREVIOUS VICTIM,
IT APPEARS THAT THE SUBJECT...

211
00:14:57,144 --> 00:15:01,148
WAS MOST LIKELY INCAPACITATED
WITH CHLORAL HYDRATE...

212
00:15:01,148 --> 00:15:03,150
AND THEN EXSANGUINATED.

213
00:15:03,150 --> 00:15:06,153
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Sighs ]

214
00:15:06,153 --> 00:15:10,658
THE DRUG WAS EITHER INJECTED
OR INGESTED,

215
00:15:11,158 --> 00:15:13,661
[ Ringing Continues ]
I'M NOT SURE WHICH.

216
00:15:13,661 --> 00:15:16,163
[ Phone Beeps ]

217
00:15:16,163 --> 00:15:18,165
SCULLY.

218
00:15:18,165 --> 00:15:20,668
[ Heavy Breathing ]
HELLO ?

219
00:15:21,168 --> 00:15:25,172
[ Gasping ]
HELLO ?

220
00:15:25,172 --> 00:15:28,676
[ Panting ]

221
00:15:38,469 --> 00:15:40,971
[ Sighs ]
WHERE WAS I ?

222
00:15:40,971 --> 00:15:42,973
STOMACH CONTENTS.

223
00:15:44,975 --> 00:15:46,977
[ Sighs ]

224
00:15:46,977 --> 00:15:50,481
STOMACH CONTENTS INCLUDE...

225
00:15:50,481 --> 00:15:52,983
PIZZA--

226
00:15:52,983 --> 00:15:56,987
[ Gasps ]
CHLORAL HYDRATE'S
IN THE PIZZA.

227
00:15:57,488 --> 00:16:00,775
THE PIZZA GUY.
[ Gasps ]
MULDER.

228
00:16:02,610 --> 00:16:04,278
MULDER ?

229
00:16:17,224 --> 00:16:19,110
[ Hissing ]

230
00:16:24,565 --> 00:16:26,901
THAT'S IT ?

231
00:16:26,901 --> 00:16:29,270
WELL, LUCKILY,
I'D GOTTEN THERE IN TIME.

232
00:16:29,270 --> 00:16:31,622
I MEAN,
THOUGH YOU WERE DRUGGED,

233
00:16:31,622 --> 00:16:34,959
YOU WERE, MORE OR LESS,
UNHARMED.

234
00:16:34,959 --> 00:16:36,827
MULDER ?

235
00:16:36,827 --> 00:16:40,247
ARE YOU OKAY ?

236
00:16:40,748 --> 00:16:44,752
WHO'S THE BLACK PRIVATE DICK
WHO'S THE SEX MACHINE
WITH ALL THE CHICKS ?

237
00:16:44,752 --> 00:16:47,154
♪♪ SHAFT ♪♪♪♪
CAN YOU DIG IT ?

238
00:16:47,154 --> 00:16:50,124
THEY SAY THIS CAT SHAFT
IS A BAD MOTHER--
SHUT YOUR MOUTH.

239
00:16:50,124 --> 00:16:52,009
TALKIN' 'BOUT SHAFT.

240
00:16:52,009 --> 00:16:53,878
I DID NOT.

241
00:16:55,830 --> 00:16:57,832
LONG STORY SHORT,

242
00:16:58,332 --> 00:17:02,870
THOUGH MY FIRST FOUR SHOTS
OBVIOUSLY MISSED RONNIE
STRICKLAND ENTIRELY,

243
00:17:02,870 --> 00:17:06,674
WITH MY FIFTH,
I WAS ABLE TO SHOOT OUT
A TIRE ON HIS CAR,

244
00:17:06,674 --> 00:17:09,176
FORCING HIM
TO ESCAPE ON FOOT.

245
00:17:09,176 --> 00:17:12,513
I LEFT YOU BEHIND,
AND I ENTERED THE WOODS
IN PURSUIT.

246
00:17:12,513 --> 00:17:16,467
I ASSUMED THAT YOU
WERE INCAPACITATED.

247
00:17:16,467 --> 00:17:18,435
THEN I HEARD SCREAMING.

248
00:17:18,936 --> 00:17:22,173
WHEN I ARRIVED IN THE CLEARING,
I FOUND THAT YOU HAD CAUGHT UP
WITH HIM FIRST...

249
00:17:22,173 --> 00:17:25,609
AND HAD... OVERREACTED,

250
00:17:25,609 --> 00:17:27,611
AND THAT HIS VAMPIRE TEETH
WERE FAKE.

251
00:17:27,611 --> 00:17:29,813
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA TELL SKINNER.

252
00:17:29,813 --> 00:17:33,267
WELL, I'M GONNA ARGUE
THAT WE CAUGHT A KILLER.

253
00:17:33,767 --> 00:17:37,521
AN UTTERLY
NON-SUPERNATURAL KILLER,
BUT A KILLER NONETHELESS.

254
00:17:38,022 --> 00:17:41,525
AND THAT YOUR ZEAL
TO CATCH UP WITH HIM
WAS AUGMENTED...

255
00:17:41,525 --> 00:17:43,761
BY THE CHLORAL HYDRATE
YOU WERE GIVEN.

256
00:17:43,761 --> 00:17:46,997
- YOU ARE AFRAID
  TO TELL THE TRUTH.
- EXCUSE ME ?

257
00:17:46,997 --> 00:17:49,366
THAT'S NOT THE WAY IT HAPPENED.
ARE YOU AFRAID IF YOU TELL IT...

258
00:17:49,366 --> 00:17:52,870
THE WAY IT REALLY HAPPENED,
YOU'LL LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT,
LIKE ME ?

259
00:17:52,870 --> 00:17:57,875
MULDER, WHY DON'T
YOU TELL ME THE WAY
YOU THINK IT HAPPENED ?

260
00:17:57,875 --> 00:18:00,377
STARTING
AT THE BEGINNING.

261
00:18:00,377 --> 00:18:02,880
YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT.

262
00:18:02,880 --> 00:18:05,382
YESTERDAY MORNING BEGAN
LIKE ANY OTHER MORNING.

263
00:18:05,382 --> 00:18:08,886
YOU ARRIVED AT THE OFFICE
CHARACTERISTICALLY
LESS THAN EXUBERANT.

264
00:18:08,886 --> 00:18:12,556
[ Quiet Tone ]
I HOPE YOU BROUGHT
YOUR COWBOY BOOTS.

265
00:18:12,556 --> 00:18:14,475
WHY ARE WE GOING
TO DALLAS ?

266
00:18:14,475 --> 00:18:18,879
ACTUALLY IT'S A LITTLE TOWN
JUST SOUTH OF THERE
CALLED CHENEY, TEXAS.

267
00:18:18,879 --> 00:18:23,167
THEY'VE HAD INCIDENTS DOWN THERE
RECENTLY WHICH I THINK YOU'LL
AGREE ARE PRETTY UNUSUAL.

268
00:18:23,167 --> 00:18:27,938
- LIKE WHAT ?
- I BROUGHT SOME SLIDES WITH
  WHICH TO BETTER ILLUSTRATE.

269
00:18:27,938 --> 00:18:31,342
HERE WE GO.

270
00:18:33,260 --> 00:18:34,979
IT'S A DEAD COW.

271
00:18:34,979 --> 00:18:38,799
IT'S ACTUALLY SIX DEAD COWS,
AND HERE'S THE REALLY
INTERESTING THING.

272
00:18:38,799 --> 00:18:41,585
WHY AM I LOOKING
AT SIX DEAD COWS ?

273
00:18:42,086 --> 00:18:46,340
BECAUSE OF THE MANNER
IN WHICH THEY DIED.  ALL SIX
WERE MYSTERIOUSLY EXSANGUINATED.

274
00:18:46,340 --> 00:18:50,778
- AND ?
- AND TWO LITTLE PUNCTURE MARKS
  RIGHT HERE ON THE NECK.

275
00:18:50,778 --> 00:18:53,397
LOOK, I GOT A SLIDE
OF THAT.

276
00:19:07,911 --> 00:19:12,266
AND, UM, ONE DEAD HUMAN VICTIM.
LAST NIGHT A VACATIONER
FROM NEW JERSEY.

277
00:19:12,266 --> 00:19:16,070
HIS BODY COMPLETELY DRAINED
OF BLOOD, AND TWO LITTLE
PUNCTURE WOUNDS ON HIS NECK.

278
00:19:20,007 --> 00:19:23,844
OKAY, LOOK, SCULLY,
I DON'T WANT TO JUMP TO
ANY HASTY CONCLUSIONS,

279
00:19:23,844 --> 00:19:27,081
BUT ON THE STRENGTH
OF THE EVIDENCE
THAT WE HAVE HERE,

280
00:19:27,081 --> 00:19:30,501
I THINK WHAT WE MAY BE
LOOKING AT IS WHAT APPEARS
TO BE A SERIES OF VAMPIRE...

281
00:19:31,001 --> 00:19:33,170
ORVAMPIRE-LIKE ATTACKS.

282
00:19:33,671 --> 00:19:36,240
ON WHAT DO YOU BASE THAT ?

283
00:19:36,240 --> 00:19:39,243
UH, WELL, ON THE CORPSES
DRAINED OF BLOOD...

284
00:19:39,243 --> 00:19:42,046
AND THE FANG MARKS
ON THE NECK.

285
00:19:42,046 --> 00:19:45,916
BUT AS ALWAYS,
I-I'M VERY EAGER
TO HEAR YOUR OPINION.

286
00:19:45,916 --> 00:19:49,186
- WELL, IT'S OBVIOUSLY
  NOT A VAMPIRE.
- WHY NOT ?

287
00:19:49,186 --> 00:19:51,872
BECAUSE THEY DON'T EXIST ?

288
00:19:51,872 --> 00:19:56,660
WELL, THAT'S ONE OPINION,
AND I RESPECT THAT.

289
00:19:56,660 --> 00:19:59,947
NONETHELESS,
I'M THINKING A MURDER
HAS BEEN COMMITTED HERE,

290
00:19:59,947 --> 00:20:02,700
AND WE CAN GO DOWN THERE
AND HELP BRING A KILLER
TO JUSTICE...

291
00:20:02,700 --> 00:20:07,220
IN WHATEVER FORM--
MORTAL OR IMMORTAL--
HE MAY TAKE.

292
00:20:07,220 --> 00:20:10,006
IT'S NOT THAT MEXICAN
GOAT SUCKER EITHER.

293
00:20:11,808 --> 00:20:14,661
[ Man Talking Quietly ]

294
00:20:14,661 --> 00:20:17,664
[ Mulder ]  UPON ARRIVING
AT THE FUNERAL HOME, I MADE
AN INTERESTING OBSERVATION,

295
00:20:17,664 --> 00:20:19,999
ONE WHICH YOU
APPARENTLY DIDN'T HEAR.

296
00:20:19,999 --> 00:20:24,170
- THAT'S A WHOLE LOT OF CASKETS.
- LARGEST IN-STOCK SELECTION
  IN THE STATE.

297
00:20:24,170 --> 00:20:28,708
WELL, WHY WOULD
A TOWN WITH A POPULATION
OF ONLY 361 NEED THAT ?

298
00:20:28,708 --> 00:20:31,694
REPEAT BUSINESS.
[ Chuckles ]

299
00:20:33,863 --> 00:20:36,149
MORTICIAN HUMOR.
EXCUSE ME.

300
00:20:40,236 --> 00:20:43,239
[ Mulder ]
APPARENTLY, YOUR MIND
WAS SOMEWHERE ELSE.

301
00:20:43,740 --> 00:20:45,491
WHOO, BOY.

302
00:20:50,196 --> 00:20:52,765
[ Exaggerated Texas Accent ]
Y'ALL MUST BE
THE GOVERNMENT PEOPLE.

303
00:20:52,765 --> 00:20:54,817
I'M LUCIUS HARTWELL.

304
00:20:58,454 --> 00:21:02,442
HE HAD BIG BUCKTEETH ?

305
00:21:02,442 --> 00:21:04,994
- HE HAD A SLIGHT OVERBITE.
- NO, HE DIDN'T.

306
00:21:06,262 --> 00:21:10,350
AND THAT'S SIGNIFICANT ?
HOW ?

307
00:21:10,350 --> 00:21:12,068
I'M JUST TRYING
TO BE THOROUGH.

308
00:21:13,202 --> 00:21:15,405
ANYWAY, THEN WE WENT
TO TAKE A LOOK AT THE BODY.

309
00:21:15,405 --> 00:21:17,590
HERE WE GO.

310
00:21:17,590 --> 00:21:19,392
NO EXAM HAS BEEN DONE ?

311
00:21:19,392 --> 00:21:23,313
NO, SIR.  THIS IS
JUST LIKE WE FOUND HIM
IN THE MOTEL ROOM, AS IS.

312
00:21:24,697 --> 00:21:27,200
NO EXAM HAS BEEN DONE ?

313
00:21:27,200 --> 00:21:29,902
UH, NO, MA'AM.

314
00:21:29,902 --> 00:21:33,740
ONCE I HEARD Y'ALL
WAS INTERESTED, I FIGURED WE'D
BEST LEAVE IT TO THE EXPERTS.

315
00:21:42,582 --> 00:21:47,170
NOW, UH, THAT CAN'T BE
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE, RIGHT ?

316
00:21:47,170 --> 00:21:51,057
IT DEPENDS ON WHAT
YOU THINK IT LOOKS LIKE,
SHERIFF HARTWELL.

317
00:21:51,057 --> 00:21:53,176
VAMPIRES HAVE ALWAYS
BEEN WITH US,

318
00:21:53,176 --> 00:21:56,162
IN ANCIENT MYTHS AND STORIES
PASSED DOWN FROM EARLY MAN.

319
00:21:56,162 --> 00:21:59,248
FROM THE BABYLONIANEKIMMU
TO THE CHINESEKUANGSHI,

320
00:21:59,248 --> 00:22:03,569
THEMOTETZ DAMOF THE HEBREWS,
THEMORMOOF ANCIENT GREECE
AND ROME,

321
00:22:03,569 --> 00:22:06,205
RIGHT DOWN TO THE MORE FAMILIAR
NOSFERATUOF TRANSYLVANIA.

322
00:22:06,205 --> 00:22:08,474
MORMO. YEAH.

323
00:22:08,975 --> 00:22:11,995
IN SHORT, SHERIFF, NO, THIS
CAN'T BE WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.

324
00:22:12,495 --> 00:22:15,365
I THINK WHAT WE'RE DEALING
WITH HERE IS SIMPLY A CASE
OF SOME LUNATIC...

325
00:22:15,365 --> 00:22:20,136
[ Chuckles ]
WHO, UH, HAS WATCHED
TOO MANY BELA LUGOSI MOVIES.

326
00:22:20,136 --> 00:22:25,341
HE WISHES THAT HE
COULD TRANSFIGURE HIMSELF
INTO A CREATURE OF THE NIGHT.

327
00:22:25,341 --> 00:22:29,128
YEAH, OKAY.

328
00:22:29,545 --> 00:22:31,330
WHAT SHE SAID,
THAT'S WHAT I'M THINKIN'.

329
00:22:31,330 --> 00:22:35,635
AND, UH, YEAH.

330
00:22:35,635 --> 00:22:38,087
STILL, THAT LEAVES US
IN SOMETHING OF A QUANDARY...

331
00:22:38,588 --> 00:22:41,691
BECAUSE THERE ARE AS MANY
DIFFERENT VAMPIRES AS THERE ARE
CULTURES THAT FEAR THEM.

332
00:22:41,691 --> 00:22:43,693
SOME DON'T EVEN
SUBSIST ON BLOOD.

333
00:22:43,693 --> 00:22:45,695
THE BULGARIANUBOUR,
FOR EXAMPLE,

334
00:22:45,695 --> 00:22:47,697
EATS ONLY MANURE.
THANK YOU.

335
00:22:47,697 --> 00:22:51,901
TO THE SERBS, A PRIME INDICATOR
OF VAMPIRISM WAS RED HAIR.

336
00:22:51,901 --> 00:22:55,004
[ Chuckles ]
UH, SOME VAMPIRES
ARE THOUGHT TO BE ETERNAL.

337
00:22:55,004 --> 00:22:57,557
OTHERS ARE THOUGHT TO HAVE
A LIFE SPAN OF ONLY 40 DAYS.

338
00:22:57,557 --> 00:23:02,178
SUNLIGHT KILLS CERTAIN VAMPIRES,
WHILE OTHERS COME AND GO
AS THEY PLEASE, DAY OR NIGHT.

339
00:23:02,178 --> 00:23:05,581
IF THERE'S A POINT, MULDER,
PLEASE FEEL FREE TO COME TO IT.

340
00:23:05,581 --> 00:23:08,034
MY POINT IS WE DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR,

341
00:23:08,034 --> 00:23:11,087
WHAT KIND OF VAMPIRE--
OR, IF YOU PREFER,

342
00:23:11,087 --> 00:23:14,090
WHAT KIND OF VAMPIRE THIS KILLER
WISHES HIMSELF TO BE.

343
00:23:26,919 --> 00:23:31,224
NOW, WHY IS IT
SO IMPORTANT THAT
HIS SHOES WERE UNTIED ?

344
00:23:31,224 --> 00:23:34,727
I'M GETTIN' TO IT.
SO WHILE YOU STAYED BEHIND
TO DO THE AUTOPSY,

345
00:23:34,727 --> 00:23:37,547
THE SHERIFF DROVE ME
TO THE TOWN CEMETERY.

346
00:23:37,547 --> 00:23:40,550
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Metal Gate Squeaking ]

347
00:23:42,051 --> 00:23:46,522
AGENT MULDER,
YOU MIND ME ASKIN' YOU
WHY WE'RE OUT HERE ?

348
00:23:46,522 --> 00:23:50,526
HISTORICALLY, CEMETERIES
ARE THOUGHT TO BE A HAVEN
FOR VAMPIRES,

349
00:23:50,526 --> 00:23:52,528
AS ARE CASTLES,
CATACOMBS AND SWAMPS.

350
00:23:52,528 --> 00:23:54,363
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY,
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY OF THOSE.

351
00:23:54,363 --> 00:23:59,001
WE USED TO HAVE SWAMPS,
ONLY THE E.P.A. MADE US TAKE
TO CALLIN' 'EM WETLANDS.

352
00:23:59,001 --> 00:24:03,206
YEAH, SO WE'RE OUT HERE
LOOKING FOR ANY SIGNS
OF VAMPIRIC ACTIVITY.

353
00:24:03,206 --> 00:24:06,876
- WHICH WOULD BE LIKE, UH--
- BROKEN OR SHIFTED TOMBSTONES.

354
00:24:06,876 --> 00:24:10,880
THE ABSENCE
OF BIRDS SINGING.
THERE YOU GO.

355
00:24:10,880 --> 00:24:13,382
'CAUSE I AIN'T--
I AIN'T HEARIN'
ANY BIRDS SINGIN'.

356
00:24:13,382 --> 00:24:15,668
RIGHT ?

357
00:24:15,668 --> 00:24:18,554
'COURSE, IT'S WINTER,
AND WE AIN'T GOT NO BIRDS, BUT--

358
00:24:18,554 --> 00:24:20,389
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE ?

359
00:24:20,389 --> 00:24:23,993
A FAINT GROANING COMING
FROM UNDER THE EARTH,
THE SOUND OF MANDICATION,

360
00:24:23,993 --> 00:24:27,346
OF THE CREATURE EATING
ITS OWN DEATH SHROUD.

361
00:24:27,346 --> 00:24:29,849
[ Rain Falling ]

362
00:24:29,849 --> 00:24:32,685
NO.  NO MANI--
MAN-- MAN--

363
00:24:32,685 --> 00:24:35,138
MANDICATION.
MANDICATION, NO.

364
00:24:35,138 --> 00:24:38,508
SHERIFF, I-I KNOW
MY METHODS MAY SEEM
A LITTLE ODD TO YOU, BUT--

365
00:24:38,508 --> 00:24:42,478
LOOK, Y'ALL WORK
FOR THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
THAT'S ALL I NEED TO KNOW.

366
00:24:42,478 --> 00:24:45,832
I MEAN, C.I.A., SECRET SERVICE.
Y'ALL RUN THE SHOW, SO--

367
00:24:46,332 --> 00:24:50,002
IT'S JUST THAT MY GUT INSTINCT
TELLS ME THAT THE KILLER
WILL VISIT THIS PLACE,

368
00:24:50,002 --> 00:24:53,623
THAT IT MAY WELL HOLD
SOME FASCINATION, SOME KIND
OF SIREN CALL FOR HIM.

369
00:24:53,623 --> 00:24:55,625
YOU KNOW ?

370
00:24:56,125 --> 00:24:57,760
[ Horn Honking ]

371
00:24:57,760 --> 00:25:00,463
HOWDY, SHERIFF !

372
00:25:00,463 --> 00:25:04,867
- OH, HEY, RONNIE.
  HOW'S IT GOIN' ?
- CAN'T COMPLAIN.

373
00:25:04,867 --> 00:25:07,036
WELL, ALL RIGHT, THEN.

374
00:25:15,494 --> 00:25:19,282
MAYBE AFTER NIGHTFALL,
SHERIFF, BUT HE'LL COME.

375
00:25:19,282 --> 00:25:21,634
OH, HE'LL COME.

376
00:25:29,241 --> 00:25:32,962
[ Mulder ]
SO WE STAKED OUT THE CEMETERY.

377
00:25:32,962 --> 00:25:36,799
[ Animal Howling ]

378
00:25:38,134 --> 00:25:40,369
MULDER.  SHOELACES ?

379
00:25:40,369 --> 00:25:43,139
HMM ?
ON THE CORPSE.

380
00:25:43,139 --> 00:25:47,276
YOU WERE GONNA TELL ME
WHAT WAS SO MEANINGFUL
ABOUT FINDING UNTIED SHOELACES.

381
00:25:47,276 --> 00:25:49,995
I'M GETTIN' TO IT.

382
00:25:53,349 --> 00:25:56,352
SUNFLOWER SEED ?
SORRY.
NO, THANKS.

383
00:25:58,838 --> 00:26:02,842
DO YOU MIND--
DO YOU MIND ME ASKIN' YOU
WHAT YOU WERE--

384
00:26:03,342 --> 00:26:06,345
HISTORICALLY, CERTAIN TYPES
OF SEEDS ARE THOUGHT
TO FASCINATE VAMPIRES.

385
00:26:06,345 --> 00:26:09,732
CHIEFLY OATS AND MILLET,
BUT, YOU KNOW, YOU GOTTA
MAKE DO WITH WHAT YOU HAVE.

386
00:26:10,232 --> 00:26:14,153
REMEMBER WHEN I SAID BEFORE
THAT WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TYPE
OF VAMPIRE WE WERE LOOKING FOR ?

387
00:26:14,153 --> 00:26:17,156
YEAH.
ODDLY ENOUGH, THERE SEEMS
TO BE ONE OBSCURE FACT...

388
00:26:17,156 --> 00:26:21,160
WHICH, IN ALL THE STORIES
TOLD BY THE DIFFERENT CULTURES,
IS EXACTLY THE SAME,

389
00:26:21,160 --> 00:26:24,446
AND THAT'S THAT VAMPIRES
ARE REALLY, REALLY
OBSESSIVE/COMPULSIVE.

390
00:26:24,446 --> 00:26:28,050
HUH.
YOU TOSS A HANDFUL OF SEEDS,
NO MATTER WHAT HE'S DOING,

391
00:26:28,050 --> 00:26:29,902
HE'S GOTTA STOP
AND PICK IT UP.

392
00:26:30,402 --> 00:26:32,905
IF HE SEES A KNOTTED ROPE,
HE'S GOTTA UNTIE IT.
IT'S IN HIS NATURE.

393
00:26:33,405 --> 00:26:36,358
THAT'S WHY I'M GUESSING
OUR VICTIM'S SHOELACES
WERE UNTIED.

394
00:26:36,358 --> 00:26:39,361
YEAH.  OBSESSIVE.

395
00:26:39,361 --> 00:26:41,197
LIKE RAIN MAN.

396
00:26:43,899 --> 00:26:47,253
WHEN THAT OLD BOY DROPPED
MATCHSTICKS, HE HAD TO
PICK 'EM ALL UP.

397
00:26:47,253 --> 00:26:50,506
SAME THING, RIGHT ?
WELL, HE DIDN'T
ACTUALLY PICK 'EM UP.

398
00:26:50,506 --> 00:26:52,875
HE COUNTED THEM.
OH, YEAH !

399
00:26:52,875 --> 00:26:55,377
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO PICK THEM UP.
247.  OFF THE TOP
OF HIS HEAD.

400
00:26:55,878 --> 00:26:57,680
IF HE PICKED THEM UP,
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN A VAMPIRE.

401
00:26:57,680 --> 00:27:01,083
YEAH.
I TELL YOU WHAT.

402
00:27:01,083 --> 00:27:05,087
I KNOW I'M IN LAW ENFORCEMENT,
BUT I'D LIKE TO TAKE HIM
TO VEGAS MYSELF.

403
00:27:05,588 --> 00:27:07,590
AM I RIGHT ?
WELL, THAT WOULD
BE ILLEGAL, RIGHT ?

404
00:27:07,590 --> 00:27:10,259
- HE WAS LIKE
  A LITTLE CALCULATOR.
- YEAH.

405
00:27:10,259 --> 00:27:12,761
[ Woman On Radio ]
YOU GOT YOUR RADIO ON ?
EXCUSE ME.

406
00:27:12,761 --> 00:27:15,598
HEY, CHARLENE.
WHAT'S UP ?

407
00:27:15,598 --> 00:27:18,100
I JUST GOT A CALL
FROM THE R.V. PARK.

408
00:27:18,100 --> 00:27:20,102
THEY GOT SOMETHING
OF A SITUATION THERE.

409
00:27:20,102 --> 00:27:23,389
SOUNDS LIKE YOU MIGHT
WANT TO HAVE A LOOK.
[ Engine Starts ]

410
00:27:58,991 --> 00:28:00,492
HEY AGAIN, SHERIFF.

411
00:28:01,977 --> 00:28:04,313
HEY AGAIN, RONNIE.

412
00:28:04,313 --> 00:28:08,117
[ Ronnie ]
I GUESS YOU GOT YOURSELF
A RUNAWAY, HUH ?

413
00:28:08,117 --> 00:28:10,619
[ Hartwell ]
YEAH, RONNIE.
I GUESS WE DO.

414
00:28:10,619 --> 00:28:13,522
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
WE OUGHT TO SHOOT
THE TIRES OUT ?

415
00:28:22,464 --> 00:28:23,966
[ Mulder ]
ANYWAY, SKIPPING AHEAD--

416
00:28:23,966 --> 00:28:26,435
WHY SKIP AHEAD ?

417
00:28:26,435 --> 00:28:28,437
WHAT HAPPENED THEN ?

418
00:28:29,855 --> 00:28:31,857
MULDER ?

419
00:28:31,857 --> 00:28:34,610
YOU SHOT OUT THE TIRES.
AND WHAT THEN ?

420
00:28:40,215 --> 00:28:42,718
[ Mulder ]
OKAY, HERE'S SOMETHING
YOU MAY NOT KNOW.

421
00:28:42,718 --> 00:28:47,723
SHOOTING OUT THE TIRES
ON A RUNAWAY R.V. IS A LOT
HARDER THAN IT LOOKS.

422
00:28:47,723 --> 00:28:50,109
I THEN TRIED
A DIFFERENT APPROACH.

423
00:28:50,109 --> 00:28:53,228
WHOA !  HEY !

424
00:28:53,228 --> 00:28:56,598
HEY, HEY !  WHOA !

425
00:28:56,598 --> 00:29:01,320
- HELP !  WHOA !
- COME ON, BIRD-DOG IT !
  THATAWAY !

426
00:29:01,320 --> 00:29:04,056
[ Screaming ]

427
00:29:04,056 --> 00:29:07,159
- OH !
- [ Groaning ]

428
00:29:07,159 --> 00:29:08,944
SHEE, OW.

429
00:29:12,081 --> 00:29:15,084
HOW YOU DOIN' THERE ?
ALL RIGHT THERE ?

430
00:29:18,971 --> 00:29:22,424
[ Engine Sputtering ]

431
00:29:29,014 --> 00:29:31,016
[ Mulder ]
FINALLY, WE PREVAILED.

432
00:29:44,196 --> 00:29:46,298
THAT'S THE SAME
AS THE OTHERS.

433
00:29:46,298 --> 00:29:48,617
RIGHT DOWN TO THE SHOES.

434
00:29:48,617 --> 00:29:51,904
[ Mulder ]
WE INTERVIEWED EVERYONE PRESENT.

435
00:29:52,404 --> 00:29:54,740
NO ONE HAD SEEN ANYTHING.

436
00:29:54,740 --> 00:29:57,643
TIRED, FRUSTRATED
AND LACKING A SOLID LEAD,

437
00:29:58,143 --> 00:30:00,145
[ Bed Vibrating ]
I JUST WANTED
TO GET CLEANED UP.

438
00:30:00,145 --> 00:30:04,149
I HAD THE SHERIFF
DROP ME AT THE MOTEL,
WHICH IS WHERE I RAN INTO YOU.

439
00:30:04,149 --> 00:30:06,652
[ Shouting ]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU WANT ME
TO DO ANOTHER AUTOPSY ?

440
00:30:07,152 --> 00:30:10,823
WHY DO I HAVE TO DO IT NOW ?
I SPENT HOURS ON MY FEET
DOING AN AUTOPSY, ALL FOR YOU !

441
00:30:10,823 --> 00:30:13,142
I DO IT ALL FOR YOU,
MULDER !

442
00:30:13,142 --> 00:30:16,545
I HAVEN'T EATEN SINCE 6:00
THIS MORNING, AND THAT WAS
WAS HALF A CREAM CHEESE BAGEL.

443
00:30:16,545 --> 00:30:18,547
IT WASN'T EVEN
REAL CREAM CHEESE,
IT WAS LIGHT CREAM CHEESE !

444
00:30:18,547 --> 00:30:22,367
NOW YOU WANT ME TO RUN OFF
AND DO ANOTHER AUTOPSY ?

445
00:30:22,367 --> 00:30:25,554
WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED TO YOU ?

446
00:30:27,740 --> 00:30:30,659
[ Mulder ]
FINALLY, YOU LEFT.

447
00:30:30,659 --> 00:30:33,662
[ Scully ]
DON'T YOU TOUCH THAT BED !
[ Door Slams ]

448
00:30:33,662 --> 00:30:36,665
[ Bed Continues
  Vibrating ]

449
00:30:52,047 --> 00:30:55,551
[ Knocking On Door,
  Door Opening ]
[ Ronnie ]  HELLO ?

450
00:30:55,551 --> 00:30:57,336
HELLO !

451
00:30:57,336 --> 00:31:00,656
OH, HEY AGAIN.
THE LADY OUTSIDE--

452
00:31:00,656 --> 00:31:02,774
SHE SAID THAT, UH,
YOU'D PAY FOR THIS.

453
00:31:02,774 --> 00:31:05,093
SHE ORDERED A PIZZA
FROM YOU ?

454
00:31:06,862 --> 00:31:09,314
EXCELLENT.  HOW MUCH ?

455
00:31:09,314 --> 00:31:11,817
12.98.
I'LL GET MY WALLET.

456
00:31:17,322 --> 00:31:20,542
- HOW MUCH ?
- IT'S 12.98.

457
00:31:23,328 --> 00:31:26,865
- OKAY, HERE'S 13.
- OKAY, THEN.

458
00:31:26,865 --> 00:31:28,867
ENJOY.

459
00:31:31,653 --> 00:31:33,538
[ Door Closes ]

460
00:31:35,540 --> 00:31:37,542
AH, SCULLY.

461
00:31:40,479 --> 00:31:42,981
[ Mulder ]
SO I ATE YOUR DINNER.

462
00:31:58,747 --> 00:32:00,949
AND THAT'S WHEN I SAW IT.

463
00:32:06,271 --> 00:32:09,274
BUT BY THEN,
IT WAS TOO LATE.

464
00:32:16,782 --> 00:32:18,750
[ Falls On Floor ]

465
00:32:21,753 --> 00:32:23,972
[ Phone Beeps, Dialing ]

466
00:32:25,290 --> 00:32:27,292
UH--

467
00:32:27,292 --> 00:32:31,179
THIS IS SCULLY.
HELLO ?
UH-- DE--

468
00:32:33,115 --> 00:32:36,284
- HELLO ?
- [ Mulder Groans ]

469
00:32:36,284 --> 00:32:39,705
UH-- UH--  TH--

470
00:32:42,157 --> 00:32:44,009
CREEP.
UHH-- UHH--

471
00:32:47,229 --> 00:32:49,097
YOU--

472
00:32:52,601 --> 00:32:54,886
[ Hissing ]

473
00:33:02,177 --> 00:33:04,062
OH, MAN !

474
00:33:05,330 --> 00:33:08,283
WHAT'D YOU HAVE TO
GO AND DO THAT FOR ?

475
00:33:12,487 --> 00:33:14,406
YOU ARE IN BIG TROUBLE.

476
00:33:17,592 --> 00:33:19,945
[ Grunts ]

477
00:33:26,451 --> 00:33:29,171
[ Mulder ]
THEN I WAS OUT COLD.

478
00:33:29,171 --> 00:33:31,840
I DON'T KNOW FOR HOW LONG,
BUT WHEN I FINALLY CAME TO--

479
00:33:33,075 --> 00:33:35,026
[ Hissing ]

480
00:33:35,026 --> 00:33:37,462
[ Scully ]
MULDER ?
[ Gun Cocks ]

481
00:33:40,165 --> 00:33:42,884
[ Growls ]

482
00:33:42,884 --> 00:33:45,871
YOU'RE SAYING
THAT I ACTUALLY
HIT HIM TWO TIMES ?

483
00:33:45,871 --> 00:33:48,690
SQUARE IN THE CHEST.
NO EFFECT.

484
00:33:48,690 --> 00:33:51,093
AND THEN HE
SORT OF FLEW AT ME
LIKE A FLYING SQUIRREL.

485
00:33:51,093 --> 00:33:53,962
WELL, I DON'T THINK
I'LL USE THE PHRASE...

486
00:33:53,962 --> 00:33:56,465
"FLYING SQUIRREL"
WHEN I TALK TO SKINNER,

487
00:33:56,465 --> 00:33:58,250
BUT, YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.

488
00:34:02,154 --> 00:34:05,891
[ Mulder ]  YOU CHECKED ON ME,
THEN LEFT TO PURSUE RONNIE
STRICKLAND INTO THE WOODS.

489
00:34:05,891 --> 00:34:10,228
ONCE I RECOVERED,
I KNEW WHAT I HAD TO DO.

490
00:34:10,228 --> 00:34:14,116
HELP ME !  HELP !

491
00:34:14,116 --> 00:34:18,537
I CAUGHT SIGHT OF HIM,
CHASED HIM OVER HILL AND DALE.

492
00:34:18,537 --> 00:34:20,372
AND IN THE END--

493
00:34:20,372 --> 00:34:23,425
[ Shouts ]

494
00:34:23,425 --> 00:34:26,128
MULDER, IT'S NOT JUST ME.

495
00:34:26,128 --> 00:34:29,131
NOBODY IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
WILL EVER BELIEVE THAT STORY.

496
00:34:31,049 --> 00:34:33,802
THEY'LL HAVE TO,
ONCE THEY EXAMINE
RONNIE STRICKLAND'S BODY.

497
00:34:37,789 --> 00:34:39,724
[ Sighs ]

498
00:34:53,138 --> 00:34:56,641
"CASE 0026198.

499
00:34:56,641 --> 00:34:59,144
RONALD LaVELLE STRICKLAND."

500
00:35:07,652 --> 00:35:10,155
PROBABLE CAUSE OF DEATH--

501
00:35:10,155 --> 00:35:12,657
GEE, THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.

502
00:35:14,659 --> 00:35:18,163
[ Grunting ]

503
00:35:28,173 --> 00:35:30,675
[ Stake Clatters On Tray ]

504
00:35:30,675 --> 00:35:33,178
[ Tools Clattering ]

505
00:35:47,742 --> 00:35:49,628
[ Hisses ]

506
00:35:53,598 --> 00:35:55,700
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Growls ]

507
00:36:02,891 --> 00:36:04,893
[ Knuckle Cracks ]

508
00:36:08,396 --> 00:36:11,733
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Woman ]  ASSISTANT DIRECTOR
SKINNER'S OFFICE.

509
00:36:11,733 --> 00:36:15,153
OH, I'M SORRY.
HE'S ABOUT TO GO
INTO A MEETING.

510
00:36:15,153 --> 00:36:18,423
YES, IT MAY LAST
SEVERAL HOURS.

511
00:36:18,423 --> 00:36:20,425
YOU'RE WELCOME.

512
00:36:20,425 --> 00:36:23,428
MULDER.  PLEASE
JUST KEEP REMINDING HIM
YOU WERE DRUGGED.

513
00:36:23,928 --> 00:36:26,431
[ Whispering ]
WOULD YOU STOP THAT ?
IT COULDN'T HURT.

514
00:36:26,431 --> 00:36:28,433
JUST STOP IT.

515
00:36:30,151 --> 00:36:32,253
SCULLY ?  MULDER ?

516
00:36:32,253 --> 00:36:35,323
I WAS DRUGGED !

517
00:36:37,575 --> 00:36:40,078
[ Sighs ]
I WANT YOU BACK IN TEXAS.

518
00:36:40,078 --> 00:36:42,847
RONNIE STRICKLAND'S BODY
HAS DISAPPEARED
FROM THE MORGUE.

519
00:36:42,847 --> 00:36:45,550
APPARENTLY IN CONJUNCTION
WITH THIS, A CORONER'S
BEEN ATTACKED.

520
00:36:45,550 --> 00:36:49,454
HIS THROAT WAS BITTEN.
THE CORONER'S DEAD ?

521
00:36:49,454 --> 00:36:52,790
NO, HIS THROAT WAS BITTEN.

522
00:36:53,291 --> 00:36:57,128
HE WAS SORT OF... GNAWED ON.

523
00:37:00,365 --> 00:37:03,468
DAYLIGHT'S BURNING, AGENTS.

524
00:37:03,468 --> 00:37:05,937
[ Door Closes ]

525
00:37:05,937 --> 00:37:08,439
WELL--  HE WAS DEAD.

526
00:37:08,439 --> 00:37:10,441
I NOTICED THAT.

527
00:37:10,942 --> 00:37:13,828
WITH A STAKE
THROUGH HIS HEART.
I NOTICED THAT TOO.

528
00:37:13,828 --> 00:37:17,465
SO WE SHOULD FIND RONNIE
OUT HERE BECAUSE ?

529
00:37:17,465 --> 00:37:21,886
BECAUSE TRADITION STATES
THAT A VAMPIRE NEEDS TO
SLEEP IN HIS NATIVE SOIL.

530
00:37:21,886 --> 00:37:24,389
OH.
YEAH.

531
00:37:24,389 --> 00:37:26,975
BUT, MULDER,
HE HAD FAKE FANGS.

532
00:37:26,975 --> 00:37:29,477
WHY WOULD A REAL VAMPIRE
NEED FAKE FANGS ?

533
00:37:29,477 --> 00:37:31,479
I MEAN, FOR THE SAKE
OF ARGUMENT.

534
00:37:31,980 --> 00:37:33,982
NO, FANGS ARE
VERY RARELY MENTIONED
IN THE FOLKLORE.

535
00:37:34,482 --> 00:37:38,486
REAL VAMPIRES AREN'T THOUGHT
TO HAVE THEM.  IT'S MORE AN
INVENTION OF BRAM STOKER'S.

536
00:37:38,987 --> 00:37:42,991
YOU WERE RIGHT BEFORE WHEN YOU
SAID THAT THIS IS A GUY WHO'S
WATCHED TOO MANY DRACULA MOVIES.

537
00:37:42,991 --> 00:37:45,827
HE JUST HAPPENS
TO BE A REAL VAMPIRE.

538
00:37:47,245 --> 00:37:49,047
[ Sighs ]

539
00:37:50,331 --> 00:37:52,800
WELL, SO WHERE
THE HELL IS HE ?

540
00:37:55,303 --> 00:37:58,806
WHAT ABOUT HIS FAMILY,
THE ONES WHO WERE GONNA
SUE US FOR 446 MILLION ?

541
00:37:58,806 --> 00:38:00,808
WELL, AN AUNT
AND AN UNCLE.

542
00:38:00,808 --> 00:38:03,194
THEIR MAIL
COMES GENERAL DELIVERY
TO A LOCAL POST OFFICE.

543
00:38:03,194 --> 00:38:06,180
NO HOME ADDRESS ?

544
00:38:09,500 --> 00:38:11,753
[ Mulder ]
THAT'S THE SHERIFF.

545
00:38:15,990 --> 00:38:19,894
- SHERIFF HARTWELL.
- EVENING, AGENTS.

546
00:38:19,894 --> 00:38:24,165
I HEARD Y'ALL WERE BACK
IN TOWN.  THOUGHT I MIGHT
BE OF SOME ASSISTANCE.

547
00:38:24,165 --> 00:38:26,667
YEAH, A-ACTUALLY
YOU CAN.

548
00:38:26,667 --> 00:38:30,505
YOU CAN STAY BEHIND HERE
WITH AGENT SCULLY WHILE I
CHECK SOMETHING OUT.

549
00:38:31,639 --> 00:38:34,559
DON'T SAY I NEVER DID
NOTHIN' FOR YA.

550
00:38:35,059 --> 00:38:37,128
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?

551
00:38:37,628 --> 00:38:41,132
WHERE MIGHT YOU BE LIVING
IF YOUR MAIL CAME GENERAL
DELIVERY AROUND HERE ?

552
00:38:41,132 --> 00:38:43,134
THE R.V. PARK ?

553
00:38:44,635 --> 00:38:46,137
YOU'RE GOOD.

554
00:38:56,697 --> 00:38:59,200
THANKS.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.

555
00:39:01,702 --> 00:39:06,207
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT VAMPIRES ?

556
00:39:06,207 --> 00:39:08,576
YOU MEAN, ASIDE FROM
THE FACT THAT I DON'T
BELIEVE IN THEM ?

557
00:39:08,576 --> 00:39:11,045
YEAH, ASIDE FROM THAT.

558
00:39:12,547 --> 00:39:16,551
WELL, THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE EXTREMELY CHARMING,

559
00:39:17,051 --> 00:39:18,553
SEDUCTIVE.

560
00:39:20,555 --> 00:39:22,924
NO, I MEAN, EVEN IF
THEY DID REALLY EXIST,

561
00:39:23,424 --> 00:39:26,928
WHO'S TO SAY THEY'D
ACTUALLY BE LIKE THAT ?

562
00:39:26,928 --> 00:39:30,431
AS AGENT MULDER SAYS,
THERE ARE MANY DIFFERENT
KINDS OF VAMPIRES.

563
00:39:30,431 --> 00:39:33,785
YEAH, THERE SURE ARE.

564
00:39:39,290 --> 00:39:41,793
I REALLY NEED TO APOLOGIZE
TO YOU ABOUT RONNIE.

565
00:39:42,293 --> 00:39:44,295
HE MAKES US ALL LOOK BAD.

566
00:39:44,295 --> 00:39:46,731
UH--

567
00:39:48,583 --> 00:39:50,918
HE'S JUST NOT
WHO WE ARE ANYMORE.

568
00:39:50,918 --> 00:39:55,857
I MEAN, WE PAY TAXES,
WE'RE GOOD NEIGHBORS.

569
00:39:55,857 --> 00:39:59,861
OLD RONNIE, HE JUST--
HE CAN'T QUITE SEEM TO
GRASP THE CONCEPT...

570
00:39:59,861 --> 00:40:01,729
OF...

571
00:40:01,729 --> 00:40:04,115
LOW PROFILE.

572
00:40:17,261 --> 00:40:19,514
BUT THOUGH HE
MAY BE A MORON,

573
00:40:19,514 --> 00:40:22,683
HE IS ONE OF OUR OWN.

574
00:40:47,926 --> 00:40:49,811
[ Cracking Sound ]

575
00:41:03,692 --> 00:41:06,144
[ Door Creaking ]

576
00:41:25,480 --> 00:41:27,933
HELLO.

577
00:41:37,893 --> 00:41:39,761
[ Creaking ]

578
00:41:39,761 --> 00:41:43,064
[ On Headphone ]
♪♪ 20th-CENTURY MAN
  THAT'S WHAT HE IS ♪♪

579
00:41:43,064 --> 00:41:46,484
- SLEEPING LATE.
- [ Growls ]

580
00:41:49,854 --> 00:41:52,824
RONNIE STRICKLAND !

581
00:41:54,109 --> 00:41:57,195
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.

582
00:41:57,195 --> 00:42:01,216
ANYTHING YOU SAY CAN
AND WILL BE USED AGAINST YOU
IN A COURT OF LAW.

583
00:42:02,500 --> 00:42:04,819
COME ON.
CUT IT OUT, RONNIE.

584
00:42:08,290 --> 00:42:11,693
[ Ronnie Grunting ]
OH, DAMN.

585
00:42:31,446 --> 00:42:34,099
BACK !

586
00:42:49,431 --> 00:42:54,836
AH, NO !
[ Screaming ]

587
00:42:58,757 --> 00:43:01,192
[ Birds Chirping ]

588
00:43:07,415 --> 00:43:09,117
MULDER ?

589
00:43:11,503 --> 00:43:15,006
[ Exhales ]
SCULLY, WHAT HAPPENED ?

590
00:43:16,975 --> 00:43:19,277
I CAME TO
IN THE CEMETERY.

591
00:43:21,613 --> 00:43:24,115
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.

592
00:43:24,616 --> 00:43:26,501
[ Horn Honks ]

593
00:43:26,501 --> 00:43:28,470
[ Car Door Opens ]

594
00:43:48,523 --> 00:43:50,992
THEY PULLED UP STAKES.

595
00:44:03,405 --> 00:44:05,340
SO THAT'S IT ?

596
00:44:05,840 --> 00:44:07,842
THEY SIMPLY DISAPPEARED
WITHOUT A TRACE ?

597
00:44:10,328 --> 00:44:13,181
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
THE WAY IT HAPPENED,
FROM START TO FINISH ?

598
00:44:17,168 --> 00:44:20,171
WELL, I CAN NEITHER CONFIRM
NOR DENY AGENT MULDER'S
VERSION OF EVENTS...

599
00:44:20,672 --> 00:44:22,173
WHICH OCCURRED
OUTSIDE MY PRESENCE.

600
00:44:22,674 --> 00:44:26,678
AND I CAN NEITHER CONFIRM
NOR DENY AGENT SCULLY'S
VERSION OF EVENTS, BUT, UM--

601
00:44:26,678 --> 00:44:28,963
ANYWAY... I WAS DRUGGED.

602
00:44:32,217 --> 00:44:34,219
THAT IS,

603
00:44:35,220 --> 00:44:38,506
ESSENTIALLY, EXACTLY
THE WAY IT HAPPENED.

604
00:44:38,506 --> 00:44:40,241
ESSENTIALLY.

605
00:44:45,747 --> 00:44:48,683
[ Mulder ]
EXCEPT FOR THE PART
ABOUT THE BUCKTEETH.

606
00:45:25,786 --> 00:45:28,356
[ Child ]
I MADE THIS !

