What's happening in Sacramento?
lfyou want to double the TV ads do that.
l just want results.
Yes, Kathy.
Sunny, John's waiting foryou.
Yeah.
What have you got for me?
This is the current trend map. Red
is ours and it doesn't look good.
Why've you given me a
bad map of goddamn India?!
Sir, you're holding it upside down.
You should just turn it.
- Red is us.
-We need to invest more on TV ads.
You are my campaign manager.
You are an idiot.
Who the hell employed this guy?
- What the hell are you doing
to my campaign? - John...
We got to get people out there!
We got to get money out there!
l've never had stress
like this, even at Harvard.
l'm thinking of chucking
it all in and leaving.
Buddy, winnen never quit.
Look on the bright side...
lt'll be the first
time in American histoy
a guy from Kerala is heading
a campaign for Governor.
True. But l'll be in the grave by the
time l get this dumb guy to win.
That's true.
You're more stressed
than at business school.
Anyway, to get this thing done,
l've offered a sacrifice to God.
What?
To shave your head.
Dude, a typical
Kerala Indian attitude!
We're the masters of backstabbing!
l'm not sure if my hair will grow back.
l'm ok with it though.
l'm ready to ty anything
to get this idiot to win.
Are you the same Sunny Kurishingal
who Time magazine called
''The Campaign Manager
with a Magic Wand''?
Sunny Kurishingal [Cross]
Now my surname means something!
l need to find a way to
increase Koy's ratings.
lf l can't find a
way to raise them,
l won't be able to sleep.
You want to raise Koy's?
How about raising yours?
Stop it.
Since your election strategies haven't
wo_ed out yet, let me give you an idea.
Evey Tom, Dick and Hary
is giving me ideas,
why keep youn back? Go ahead.
Why don't you talk with your
friend, Francis Kunjappan?
The great Public Works minister
in Kerala, aka ''God's Own County''?
God's Own County?
Devil's Own Rulers!
Francis Kunjappan...
Only l know his true
face: Fraud Number 1 .
You're not tying to mary
your daughter o_ to him...
lt's to win the elections.
Frauds like him will be pe_ect.
You ask him. He'll
give you some ideas.
What can he do?
He would've passed his eighth grade
if he hadn't failed eight times.
The person who secures good grades
becomes a civil servant there
and the one who hangs around, throwing
stones at buses, is his governor.
That's India for you.
Come on, politics is
the same eveywhere.
Back home, thieves
wear a shirt and dhoti
here they wear a suit and tie.
l've said my piece.
Someone from Kerala for US politics?
Why not? NASA, Apple,
Microsoft, doctor, engineer...
For brains, the US o_en
use people from back home.
Whereas people from Kerala specialize in
backstabbing, cheating and so on.
Listen, what did Steve Jobs say?
''Stay hungy, think di_erent.''
Maybe, maybe....
Yes, yes. The report says there's
no problem in the structure ofthe dam.
What can we do then?
- l'll hand you over.
- Who?
- Sunny Kurishingal from America.
- Please call me later.
Hello. Who is this? The King ofAmerica?
So, Mr ''Emerging Kerala'',
what makes you call me?
Can't l call the Public Wo_s minister of
Kerala evey day to ask what he had for lunch?
- What's new in Kerala?
- Same old news.
When it's hot, it's a power cut..
Rain? Problems with
the Kerala Dam.
- Our dam? - It's not a dam. It's like
the snake round Lord Shiva's neck.
Remove it, you get bitten;
but you can't leave it there.
Money. Money.
Have you brought all of it?
- Not here
- There are hidden cameras around.
l was talking to someone here.
So, what's new in America?
lt's an avalanche of news here.
California State Election. l'm
working to make our candidate win.
Actually that's
why l called you.
l need your help.
My friend. If l step aside now
to play American politics
then l can never return.
l'll spend my life running
a tea shop in LA.
No, no. What l
meant was this,
l need someone to help
sort this crap out here.
Someone like a consultant.
Money isn't a problem. l'm ready
to spend whatever it takes.
There are only two people in Kerala
with the brains for that sort ofthing.
One ofthem is me
but l can't come.
- The other person? - The other is
also me and l can't come either.
lt's time for a meeting now.
l'm hanging up.
- Ok, l'll call you. - Think about
what l said. - Bye, bye.
- Please.
- Hold this.
Welcome, welcome.
Sir, please sit.
Please sit.
- Where were we?
- Let the central report stand.
- Stand where?
- Whatever you say. The people of
Kerala.... - Let it be. One minute.
Please don't murder Tamil.
Please speak Malayalam.
Central committee report...
clearly says no...
damage to the dam...
and there is no...
threat right?
Yes. Threat.
So it's ok to murder
English then?
- No but...
Anything can be written
in the report.
But the people in Kerala are scared.
What do we
tell the media?
We aren't able to sleep here.
- The area around the dam will
become a desert! - Sir...
- Don't stop my flow. - You've been
saying the same thing over and over.
Kerala people?! But what
will Tamil people do?
No solution. No coming.
- Who will solve it when they strike?
- Sir...
They keep tying to
make us understand.
Shall l talk to them? You
don't have to. Come.
The ego of these people.
lt's like that. When there's a problem,
all parties in Tamil Nadu gang together.
- Here, it's backstabbing.
- That's right.
Forget it. Do we have
a solution to this nonsense?
Now that all our
ideas have flopped,
shall we consult Jaganathan?
You mean the guy who wants to
take my job? Isn't there anyone else?
We haven't been able to do
anything for the past four days
so the Chief Minister
is vey anxious.
The only thing you're good for
is standing there wearing
a starched shirt.
You look good, but there's
nothing in your head.
Okay, okay. Call that
annoying Jaganathan.
Four...
lt's not a four. Just two!
l'll give you mo.
What?
- l'll give you mo.
- Not acceptable!
lt's four. The
stone's the bounday.
You change the
rules as you go along.
When we batted, the
tree was the bounday.
Don't behave like a bad sport
when l hit a bounday.
Hey umpire. What are you
standing there for?
- l signaled four already.
- Yes. It's a four. Go.
- Go bowl the next ball.
- The big ''bandicoot'' team...
Listen, don't get bowled
out and humiliated.
Just pay the bet and leave.
You'll never learn no matter
how many times we beat you.
There is still one ball le_.
You go bowl.
Let them play. They must
score eight o_ one ball!
lt's Impossible so
Iet's see how they win.
Eight runs from one ball. Don't
expect me to bowl a No Ball.
Eight runs from one ball?
Hello...
Oh. One second, Sir.
Boss! Boss!
Minister Francis Kunjappan. He wants
to talk to you. It's an emergency.
To hell with Kuniappan.
lf l losethis, l might
as well leave the county.
l'm under pressure here. Don't come
to me with Kunjappan now.
Sir? He's dealing with another
big problem here at right now.
He'll call you back soon.
Hold this.
Come on. Hold this.
Give.
He's folding his dhoti.
Game on!
- Come on. Bowl.
- Hey, hey...
Don't over do it. It's
difficult to get an eight.
l didn't want the dhoti
to get in the way when l run.
- l just said that for a build up.
- Hey...
No, no. l'm not doing it.
Are you ready?
Bowl.
Cows.
- Cow! Cow! - He thinks he's
the national team captain.
Catch the ball! Quick, quick!
Run and catch it!
Run! Fast!
Don't stop running!
lt doesn't matter if it's in a cow pat.
Get the ball!
Quick! Quick!
Run!
Come on! Run!
Get the ball and throw it! Quick!
You come and take it ifyou want! My
mom'll kill me if l touch cow dung!
Run!
We iust need mo more runs.
We won!!!
What a game!
Boss, that was great.
You can never beat us.
Hey!
Winning or losing is not
important in a game.
Participate. Taking
part is important.
l just said that because l got the chance.
Please forgive me.
Go and buy something that
will make your belly ache.
-And us? - l'll give you something
that won't make your belly ache
Something that doesn't
make your belly ache.
Boss, that's a good one!
Just a minute. One minute.
Can't you see what it says?
''Don't spit here.''
lt's in English.
It's for foreignen.
l'm from Kerala. l can spit.
- Do you want to spit?
- No, it's okay.
- Bless you.
God bless.
Jaganathan. Come. Sit
- Jaganathan! Can l get you some co_ee?
- No, l just had some.
ln short. Neither pam is ready
to decide on the Kerala Dam issue.
They are...
- Both parties want to get out ofthis.
- No. They...
Do one thing.
From tomorrow, charge all visitors from
other states to our Sabari Mala temple,
a five thousand rupee tax
on their offerings to God.
Tax offerings to God?
This man is talking nonsense.
Give us something
feasible at least.
Francis. Please send
this boy outside.
Send him out. Don't
annoy him.
l was the one who suggested calling him.
Now l'm out.
l should learn
politics from him.
He's gone.
lfwe announce this tax, the media in
other states will make this an issue.
They'll stir things up on all
the current a_ain programs.
This is a risky move Jaganathan.
But how will it help?
Redirection. Do people watch breaking
news until the stoy is over?
ln our county, the men watch breaking
news as much as the women watch soaps.
When they turn on the TV,
they want to see something new.
Politicians and sex scandals, businessmen
and bribey, sports stars and drugs,
film awards and nepotism, drug companies
and hush ups, big business and pollution.
ln time, they're forgotten. No one
cares about yesterday's news.
People once involved in huge scandals
live here as role models now.
lndian people are forge_ul.
People aren't donkeys;
they won't buy it.
People have elected many
donkeys as ministen here.
Our boss is a smart cookie.
Boys, you've got to use yourfeet to
play football, not yourfingers.
There's been strong objection against
Kerala to the recently introduced tax
from Tamil Nadu and other states.
This decision has been made because ofthe
financial situation our state is facing.
l humbly request brothers from
the Tamil and other states
not to consider this an expense and to
co-operate with us to enforce this tax.
This has shocked all Sabari
Mala devotees of Tamil Nadu.
''Tax on the offerings to God.''
As always, you escaped thru
Jaganathan's brilliance!
Change the channel.
- Changed... Show this energy in politics!
- Jaganathan! You..!
What he said is true.
Eveyone's forgotten the dam
and are talking about this tax.
He used to think about sports.
You brought him into politics.
See what's happened,
he's treating politics
like a sport now.
That's true.
His idea wasn't all that great.
- That's also true. - Even small
children now... - No, no!
Shut up.
Did you get this idea when people from other
states were scrapping here forfour days?
lts betterwe cut
Jaganathan o_ at the root.
Whatever he touches
turns to gold.
lt's cheap to create one
problem to escape from another.
That is so right.
This can only happen in our county.
Nowhere else.
Anywhere else, he'd
be behind bars.
Rewind what you said.
- Bars?
- Behind bars...
Not the bars. Rewind
a little more.
- This wouldn't happen in another county.
-Another county! That's a good point.
- This is why you're called a lioness.
- That is also right.
Don't clap.
My ratings are
down the hole too.
l'm working on it John. l'm tying
to get a consultant from India.
- Yeah. Whatever.
- Trust me John.
Your fault!
Go do some goddamn work!
Hey, Go get the club!
Come on, come on, come on!
Emerging Kerala.
- Thank God.
- Hello.
l apologize for troubling you.
lt's urgent. Please can you do
something about my problem?
lfyou can, l'll build a Taj
Mahal foryou in Kerala.
ln that case, start looking
for a plot of land.
l don't want money. Tell me what
you will give me personally.
What's happening?
Flirting in the sun?
- Is this a new scandal?
- No she's my friend's wife.
The minister is waiting foryou. He's
playing a weird game with sticks and balls.
Put the ball so l
can hit it easily.
Place it on the tee.
Hello Jaganathan. Get a club.
Let's play.
- No. l am used to playing
with bigger balls. -True...
lt's di_icult to hit
this into the hole.
These days, we've got to learn this
to meet big shots in the county.
- Sathyasheela, get Jaganathan a beer
from the cooler. - No it's okay.
l don't mix games and drinks.
That's a good sportsman.
By the way,
the government gave you the land,
foundations are laid. It's been mo years.
What happened to
your sports academy?
Have you lost
interest in it?
l have some financial issues. But
l have to start work this year.
There are only mo years before
a new government comes in.
Build the academy and
start classes before that
otherwise the next government will build
a mall there. That's the trend now.
Move aside. Please move aside.
This is a special kind of shot.
That was just a rehearsal. The
real shot isjust coming.
l asked him to put
the ball on the tee.
l don't believe it when you
say you don't have money.
There are many ways
to make money.
This sports academy is
notjust a building.
lt is a place where the dreams and
futures of people can be forged.
l'm adamant that the money that goes into
building it has to be earned honestly.
l know you're adamant about certain
things. That's why l called you.
A_er all, you've pulled me out
from a tight spot more than once.
Don't l have to do something
for you in return?
Athree month iob.
Three hundred million rupees.
Location: America.
Currency dollars...
five million dollars!
Do you want to give it a go?
Let's rock. Let's
stir things up.
Let's fly high.
lf you stand against him.
You'll be turned to ashes.
Let's fight and win.
Let's fight and fly higher
with the wind of change...
Oh, dream that was nurtured
for days, stand by my side.
Let's rock. Let's
stir things up.
Let's fly high.
Please give our students a
Iecture about swimming.
l'll meet you in person later
and give you the details.
Ok?
Ok. Thank you so much.
- Who is it?
- What?
Kutral Easwar. Do you know him?
l know. Isn't he that
thug from the south?
- You're right!
- l know him.
You know Britney Spean
and Justin Bieber...
but not Kutral Easwar!
He's an Indian!
Kutral Easwar. The youngest man in
India to win the highest sports award.
He swam across evey sea in
the world within a year.
He was the future of India.
Lately, he is doing some job in
America as he didn't get a sponsor.
He is brainy. That's why
he stopped swimming.
There is no shortage of
brainy people in India.
We're short of shame.
Our population is the
biggest in the world...
but we're bottom ofthe
Olympic medal tally.
lf population gromh were a sport, India
would've won more medals than anyone.
lsn't that why we're
building a sports academy?
Just an academy is not enough forthat.
People's mentality needs to change.
People must understand there
are other sports as good as cricket
and that you can live happily here
even if you play those games too.
That's also why l've
accepted thisAmerican trip.
l wonder why the people in America
are asking foryour help.
Only local countymen like you
don't value me.
America is a county
that respects brains.
Don't you need a passport?
No.
These days they askfor
libray cards at the airport.
God! Are these the ones who are
going to come with me to America?
White birds in the sty flew across to
the festival packed with elephants.
The heavy clouds that were
a burden to the shoulders
have moved on a_erthe
showers ofthe monsoon.
Let's go across the banks ofthe
river and play rhyming games!
Let's jump into the sea,
get soaked and go fishing!
Let's reap harvests! Let's
make our dreams come true!
Let's raise our flags in our
colomul path, like excited birds!
Let's rock! Let's
stir things up!
Let's fly high!
The breeze that comes
along with the rain
danced to the beating
of sweet fingen.
The magic bird, the
lightning and the fish
spread light and gave us
flowen of the night.
Let's solve the puzzle
of eveyone's stoy.
Let's change the
tactics of our game.
Experience is my teacher.
Let's learn from them and win.
Let's sing another song, march
like soldien and spread laughter.
Let's rock! Let's
stir things up!
Let's fly high!
Let's fight and fly higher
with the wind of change
Oh, dream that was nurtured
for days, stand by my side.
ls yourwheel pulling
you to the side?
- Look Chief! Bar!
- Oh, shall we go get some lemon juice?
- Don't waste time.
- Waste time?
lt is said, that you can't
get back time lost.
But a_er an 18 hour flight to the US,
you land on the same day you started.
- Let's go. - You want to start now?
There's alcohol on the flight!
Those are the main fireworks.
These are samples.
Lets drink before and
during the trip.
Should l get rid ofthem?
What are you looking at?
There is a big secret that l
haven't told you till now.
What secret is that?
Don't keep us in suspense.
- Tell us.
- When l was young...
- l was in love with a girl. Jessi.
- Who? - Jessi
Love was her weakness.
She loved me so much.
She also loved a filmmaker next
door as much as she loved me
and then she eloped with another
guy who was another neighbor.
But before she le_...
- She made me promise something.
- What promise?
That l would consider all Indians
as my brothen and sisters.
A promise might be nothing for her.
But for me,
l find it di_icult enough to break
an egg, let alone a promise.
And because Indians are my brothers and
sisters... l can't even date or mary one!
- Did you hear what he said?
- Forget about it...
A_er all, no Indian woman
could match you. True?
- Hey...
- What?
We'll find an American girl with
golden hair, co_ee brown eyes
and red lips, carying a lamp, and
who'll walk so_ly into your house.
We'll make sure that happens.
- He needs 'pleasure' in his life too.
- What?
- You mean 'marriage' in life?
- Yes. Kids. Family and responsibilities.
Listen, within a year
there'll be kids running
around your house.
- That's right.
- Come on.
The air hostesses will
be beautiful right?
Are they the ones we
saw in skirts?
Let go of me.
- It's because l'm scared. - Ifyou're
scared, you shouldn't have come.
Welcome.
- She's wearing a sari.
- l'm not coming.
l know.
- l am Jabbar Pottakuzhi. Actually...
- Come here.
Are we on the wrong flight?
See, an African air hostess.
What's wrong with you guys?
This is my ticket.
- Can't we sit here?
- Sit there. Sit.
He put it in his mouth.
Did you see this. He's
making fun of me.
Don't laugh at me.
l'll get o_the flight.
Be quiet or they'll ask you to leave
the flight. They're notorious for it!
What's this old lady saying?
She's telling us what to
do ifthe plane crashes.
What? Don't scare me.
l'm already sitting
here frightened.
lt's like giving a discount
card for the mortuay
to patients going into
the operating theater.
The liquor is here. Miss, two
double brandies and soda for me.
- Miss...
- Whisky.
ls there any le_?
- Enjoy your drink.
- Thank you.
Two double brandies for me.
Two double brandies.
We can get as much as we
want in fint class, right?
Don't gulp it like it's water.
- This is fine stuff. Show it
some respect. - Will l get more?
Miss, one more please.
Here, don't you want the glass?
Don't be greedy. What will
that air hostess think?
Air hostess? They were air hostesses 20
years ago. Now they are air grannies.
lnstead offlirting with them,
l'd rather drink and pass out.
-Am l not right?
- Be quiet. Don't make so much noise.
- If you are quiet, they'll give you a
Iot of liquor. - Dude, check her out.
They touched my entire body
at the security check.
Varkie didn't you tell
me there are gays here?
l thinkthey were. Lucky for me,
l put on underwear today.
- Finally you listen to me.
- Leave it...
They don't know that Jabbar
Pottakuzhi is a VIP.
Nobody is safe. They even frisked our
ex-president when he visited last year.
Do something.
Start a protest now.
- Protest? As if he'll do it.
- What? They spoke to me in English.
lf it had been our language, l'd
have given them a mouthful.
- Yeah, right! - Didn't l protest
in our local railway station?
- This isAmerica.
- Shut up.
Let's see how we can find Sunny.
Let's use the pass
phrase spies used to use.
- It rains in Moscow this time ofyear.
- It rains in Moscow this time of year.
lt rains in Moscow this time ofyear.
lt rains in Moscow this time of year.
But not in Prague.
- Hi. l'm Sunny.
-Jaganathan.
- Welcome to America.
- He looks like a Bollywood actor.
- This is Jabbar. - Hi Mr. Jabbar.
- This is Varkie.
- Hello. Hi.
- Hello Va_ie. Come on let's go.
Look. A train driving on the road.
That's a car. A limousine
This is why l ask you to
watch English movies.
He watches English movies. But they
don't have can and bikes in them.
Some ofthem don't
even have sound.
Don't make fun of me.
- That's my weakness.
- Get in.
What si_ Is this your
house or your ca_
You're funny Jaganathan.
Either l should do comedy or action.
That's what they like.
- Yes.
- So...
- How was the flight?
- Ok.
The flight was good but
they gave us rabbit food.
We can fix that. There is a nice Italian
restaurant in the hotel you're staying.
They have great pasta.
My tongue has been dead for the
past days eating lettuce leaves.
lf l have pasta now l'll have
to place a wreath on it.
Can you arrange for a
little rice and fish cury?
Otherwise l reckon l'll be
dropping rabbit poo tomorrow.
- l'll do one thing. l'll ask my wife
to make it for you. - That's great!
Sir, do they have
liquor shops here?
... and do they stand
in line there?
What's this?
This is a Rubik's cube.
My stress reliever.
- What?
- l use it when l'm stressed.
When l was in tenth grade l
heard of a cube in mathematics.
ls it that?
l've heard of cube too.
l know. Ice cube.
lce cube! We find it in the ice
factoy and it's used in the bar.
lsn't the building Bin
Laden knocked down here?
Bin Laden... Stop your nonsense.
These women are gorgeous...
such eye candy!
Stare gracefully.
- You guys stay here, l'll be
back in five minutes. - What?
- l'll be back in no time. Five minutes.
- We'll just look around.
- Varkie. That's an awesome figure.
- Just come along.
Ah. Emerging Kerala.
- Hello.
- What did l ever do to you..
to give me such trouble?
- What happened?
- You're asking me what happened?
This is like county bums going into the
city. They're creating a scene here.
Are these guys supposed
to help us win?
That's iust appearances.
Jaganathan is cleverwith
pe_ect political acumen.
And the othertwo with him;
behind big people you always
find dumb people like them.
He's just a little short tempered
otherwise, he's a nice man.
Eveything will be alright.
You'll see.
- Things will get better.
- l hope they do.
This is like adding
fuel to the fire.
l've heard trouble
finds you in many ways.
But this time it's
come by plane.
America!
Wow, sex!
The last sheet is also gone.
These people only have paper here. How
will l write a complaint without a pen?
l have to complain that
there's no water.
Allah. God. This is bad.
l have to get a big bucket
and a mug tomorrow.
Wine glass?
America. WhatAmerica?
There's no water in the toilet.
Wait and watch, l'll leave
behind halfthe glass ofwater.
My name is
Sudhi!
Your name is Meenu Kum!
Meenu Kutty!
Sudhi!
Tell me the vowels.
- Mammal?
- No, no, no, no.
- Vowels!
- Oh!
Co_ee?
What's your name?
- What's your name?
- Lisa.
- Pi_a, good name.
- No, no, Lisa.
l've heard of Monalisa.
No no lisa?
l'm poor English.
Oh. Paul English. Nice name.
Not my name. My
name is Jaganathan.
Chacko Nathan?
Not Chacko Nathan. Ja - Gan - Na - Than
Sory...
Excuse me.
America is definitely user friendly.
To answer her call
she asks to be excuse! d.
- Jagan.
- l'm here.
You're not ready yet?
John is waiting for our meeting.
- Ready.
- Wearing a shirt and dhoti?
l'm comfortable in this.
Plenty of room for fresh air.
lf l wear a suit and tie, it's
like someone's choking me.
- How do l look?
- Super, right?
Before you couldn't a_ord
dhotis and now look at you!
Didn't l tell you yesterday? You
have to be in suit for a meeting with John.
l don't want to...
- No. - You'll look great in a suit.
- No way.
You tell him.
You must wear a suit in America.
- We'll fix this.
- It's time to go.
l told you that dress code
is vey important here.
- The glasses are great.
- Listen to me.
See. You people do
not value me.
But these people dressed in suits and ties
have called me for a problem they can't solve.
You're great!
Hi Sunny. Good morning.
What's up?
He's our PR and marketing guru.
Second in command, Andy.
Hello.
- Undee? Underwear?
- Excuse me. My full name is Sachidanandan.
How did you change
that kind of a name?
O_icially, l'm Sachidanandan.
When l was doing my MBA
my friends called me Anand.
When l started working with
Sunny, it became Andy.
Different decorations
in di_erent countries.
There's nothing wrong
in decorating yourself
as long as you know
who the real you is.
l just said that because
l got the chance.
- Yeah, yeah! - Ok, have fun!
- Come.
l'll call you back.
Welcome to America.
Don't wory! l'm ok!
Ok eveybody!
You ok?
l recogniM you.
Mr. Jaganaggi.
lt's such a pleasure to meet you. Sunny
has told me eveything about you.
John. This is Jaganathan.
l recogniM you. Mr. Naggajaggy.
Sunny has told me all about you.
We're going to create
histoy together.
You and l are going to make the
most ofwhat we've got here.
l'm a modest man and you
can help me make it.
- Did you understand what he said?
- No.
Well...
Ok...
We came just because Sunny told me.
We are notjobless people from India.
lfyou want to know about us,
you can go there and inquire.
We'll fix eveything for you.
You talk him. He talk me.
How is it?
l'll explain to you later.
Oops! My phone! Excuse me!
Excuse me!
Ok, ok.
Why is he blabbering in English like an
Australian captain who's won the toss.
Any problems?
No no. Only solution. Solution.
ln a minute, he spoke the amount
of English that l speak in a year.
Can you guys stay out for mo minutes.
l'll just speak to John and come back.
Now l get it.
Bush.
- With him? Bush?
- Oh Bush!
The doors... push. Come on.
No phone calls.
Just take messages.
l first want to know about
the elections here.
The governofs post is generally given to
physically challenged people in our county.
They have elections for that here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Well actually. The governor here is like
the chief minister back in our county.
So, the chief minister
of Kerala is...
...is the governor here.
So the governor here
is the chief minister there?
Let me come to the point.
There are only mo parties here.
Republicans and Democrats.
We are Republicans.
Which is indicated
by the red spots.
Currently there are more
blue spots than red spots.
lt's because the counties favoring
us, in your language 'districts',
are vey few.
The reason? Our candidate is John Koy
and his public rating is vey bad.
Our objective is to increase the number of
these red spots. That's why you're here.
Excuse me.
You brought our boss
here for such a silly thing?
Get some red stickers and put them
overthe blue ones. Problem solved.
Brilliant.
- Koy's rating will rise.
- No, it won't!
Who is John Koy's opponent?
Who is it?
lt's a guy called George Hope.
Who?
Any solutions?
He looks like our
Iocal builder
with those glasses
and that gray moustache.
You first need a problem
to solve to gain votes.
A good politician is one
who solves a problem.
Let's start with a problem
that always works in India.
Caste.
We don't have any issues like that.
Where is caste in the States?
ls there a county
without caste issues?
Historically there have been many
problems between blacks and whites.
- Now there's less of a problem.
- That's enough.
- Blood comes out easily from
unhealed wounds.- Yeah, yeah.
Assuming we execute your idea,
how do you plan to implement it?
l can give you any
number of ideas.
But the consequences
ofwhat we do
should land on opponent
George Hope's head.
Right now we have reports from Compton of
race riots, bemeen whites and blacks...
over a whole bunch of issues we're
not getting a clear account of.
We're going to go live now to John Koy on the
scene bringing both these communities
together.
Let me say this. There's no place
for racial disharmony in my county.
We are all brothers, and
if you are girl, sisters.
Like the keys on my piano keyboard.
We play the tunes together.
Bobby Marley. One
of my favorites.
- Cheers.
- My glass didn't clink.
Congrats Jagan. Koy
is a happy man.
Our ratings have gone above
Hope's for the fint time.
When our boss places his hand on
something, the rest is histoy.
Not only in America. Human
beings are same eveywhere.
ln evey group, they only point
out mistakes in others.
Religion, caste, language.
A whole lot of
unnecessay things.
Sir, when the boss is drunk
he talks philosophy.
l just said that because
l got the chance.
My beautiful girl, l haven't
seen you for a day.
Disappointed...
How is eveything?
- Hey beautiful, what's your name?
- Kimberly
- What did she say?
- Kaarthumbi.
Will you mary me? You will be the
Princess of Kerala, God's Own County.
l'm sory. l have a
partner already.
Who is that snow white?
Match has been
abandoned due to rain.
lt's okJagan.
She's a lesbian.
- FBl?
- Not FBl. Lesbian.
Which means she's
attracted to women.
lf all the beautiful girls
are attracted to other girls...
what will the men do?
That is why they don't
bother to look at us.
- Ok. l'm making a move.
- Give it here. l'll deal with this.
Don't wory.
- We'll come when it gets a little
darker. - Us too.
You leave, Sir.
Ok take care guys.
- Be safe.
- Take care.
Boss! Boss!
Please...
Happy days in America.
Your eating and drinking
is going well.
Yes. It's going well.
l asked you to set me up
with an American girl
and you still leave me
hung - hung - hungy.
l blame myselffor giving you
guys this responsibility.
Boss. The fair ladies' hair
here is like coconut husks.
But, the hair ofthe
women in our county...
Wouldn't it be kicking ifyou saw them with
flowers in their oiled hair like our girls?
-A promise might be nothing foryou.
But for me...- Please...
- We've heard a lot of this.
- Can you stop it?
Who put this post here?
lsn't this that guy?
Vasco de Gama
- The guy we know. Vasco de Gama.
- l'll give Vasco de Gama some trouble.
No, Boss! Don't piss here!
This is America!
- Don't people piss in America?
- Not in public places.
- Dude, he's drunk.
- Yeah, he's totally wasted.
Let's call a taxi and take him home. Unless you
want to eat breakfast in an American prison.
Then call a taxi.
Hey bro, you have a lot of
admirals in Kerala.
-Admiren, not admirals! - Yes
you have many admirers.
Please wait here. Don't go anywhere.
Come on. Let's
get a taxi. Taxi!
Call a taxi. Taxi!
1 ,OOO dollan? We are Indians.
Poor. 750 ok?
- No.
- Hey. Please, please, please...
750 ok?
Any promotional o_ers
for new customers?
- 750 ok?
- Please. Accept.
When brother is here, you should consider
your sister-in-law as your mother.
750 ok? Please, please
Please, please, please.
- Please. Ok?
- Ok.
What a handsome beast!!!
You didn't introduce me to them.
- What?
- You didn't introduce me to them.
l said...
l'm his political assistant.
Ok, and him?
He's his plain assistant.
-We came in a plane.
- l didn't say that.
Jabbar Pottakuzhi. Come on.
How old are you?
Varkie. Varkie.
- Come here.
- The Boss is calling you. Go.
Go sit there.
Was it for this?
You're the political assistant,
you can sit on the floor.
Talk.
Boss.
What's your name?
My name is Jessi.
- Boss. What happened?
- Jessi.
- Oh Jessi.
- What's the matte_
- No... One...
One matter name is Jessi.
That's the only matter.
- But nice name.
- Thank you.
- Lovely smile.
- Ya, ya.
By the way, what's your name?
My name is Jaganathan.
Call me Jaggu.
- Jaganathan.
- Oh...
Can l call you Jacks?
- Jacks? Yeah. That's a dog's name.
- Jacky.
Jacky. Jacky, the giant killer!
- Why this bad, bad, things you're...
- Tell.
Basically l'm from
a poor family.
My husband, he ran away from me.
l've a child, lot
of debts and...
that's the reason l
am into all this.
Boss. What is she saying?
She said her husband le_ her
and went with someone else.
All ofthem have
the same resume!
Poor girl. She does
not know anything.
750 multiplied by 30.
Ok...
750 by thim.
l give payment for one month.
l book you.
You have only one iob.
Love me. Romance.
But no outgoing!
- Yeah. No going.
- Ok, love me...
l pay dollan. You give romance.
- Sure, but...
- No...
No butt...
l want only heart.
Please.
l've heard of love
at first sight...
According to the boss, it's
Iove eveything at sight.
He's got an award from the
Indian president for this thing.
The clouds get denser
Desires start to pour
and l hear a new melody in my heart.
With whom should we begin ourjourney?
With whom should we share our pain?
With whom should we share our life?
You never know.
Ok great. Our campaign
is gaining momentum now.
lfwe maintain this,
we're sure to win.
- Ok let's move to the next project.
- What is it?
We have to give
people some freebies.
Proiect ''Free''.
How about a TV?
TV? Don't you read the
papers back home?
They give TVs, fridges, and washing
machines for free in the elections there.
According to American
standards, you should
give them at least a
Range Rover or a Humvee.
Or else, let it be a free trip to the moon.
That's the fashion now.
We have to win. But aren't these
cheap, silly, and shameless things?
Are you Mr Pemect? Ifyou are
ashamed, you shouldn't be in this.
The end is important, not the means.
That's how it is in our county!
Send this man out.
He's talking nonsense when the boss
is saying something important.
- Creating an idea is not easy.
-Andy...
- Let me handle this.
-Are you sure? - Yeah...
- Mr Pe_ect.
- Idiots.
- Sunny these guys will ruin you.
- Get lost man.
- Did he abuse us in English?
Boss, he's gone.
- l'm fine. Bit expensive.
- Ok.
We'll have to spend plenty.
Let's win first. l'll teach you how
to earn this money back in mo weeks.
But l'll need extra commission forthat.
In dollars.
l really like to think of ourselves
as compassionate Republicans.
We give iPods, iPhones,
automobiles to various people...
and in return, they'll make
money for this county.
lf you do not want this
county to succeed...
you are not a patriot. You
are not a true American.
This is an outrage.
He can't do that.
Oh yeah. All the way to
election day they can do it.
lnstead of bringing India up
to American standards,
You're bringing America
down to Indian standards.
l'm done with this farce.
Ok...
Now l realize where all the
rice in our county goes...
They eat so much, but
still look like liards.
Jacks. Stop talking in Indian language.
l don't understand at all.
When you listen to the word 'lndia',
your heart should feel proud.
When you listen to the word 'Kerala',
your soul should swell.
Do you understand?
Obviously not.
You are really funny.
Welcome. Welcome. Namaste.
Oh. Hindi speaking Chinese.
Namaste.
- You wanna look at this?
- Yeah.
iPhone. Good choice. See this?
No, no. Don't wory.
This is what you want.
Duplicate.
See! Super strong!
Like you.
- Thank you. - But Jacks these
things have no warranty at all.
But life itself has no warranty.
Duplicate shop. But
great philosophy.
l like you...
Give me anything...
- l'll make a duplicate.
- Ok...
Make a duplicate ofthis girl.
Jessi.
Huh? Jacks!
You know what? l really like you.
- Let me show you something.
- Ok.
Jacks we have to go somewhere.
- Jacks no, listen to me.
- Come on.
Why are you doing this Jacks.
Jacks let's go, no?
- My uncle.
- Your uncle?
Jackie Chan, his uncle? These guys are
betterthan us when it comes to lying.
- It's notjust all rugs.
- Ok. - Not bad.
- Don'tjudge a book by its cover.
- What's that?
Duplicate. What's your name?
What's your name?
- Call me Dupe Lee.
- Dupe Lee?
- Ok. Thank you Dupe Lee. - You're
welcome.
- Bye. - l'll see you later.
Now thatAndy has joined George Hope's
campaign, we have to be more careful.
Why? Anyway, now that he's gone there,
l'm sure they'll lose.
lt's my wife. She's invited
you all for dinner.
Has she? In that
case l want pi_a.
- Burgerfor me.- Burger? In that case,
burger for me too. It tastes good.
You've been here just a few days
and you've already become American?
No wonder people from Kerala don't
return when they come here.
lt's disappointing. Sunny, in
that case l'll have burger too.
l ordered burger, piza, hot dogs, and some
bread with meat, in our hotel room yesterday
l've named this
sticker girl, ''Spom''.
Excuse me guys.
l don't know ifyou understand
the seriousness of this.
l've lost my right hand, Andy.
And there's less than 150/o chance
ofwinning now. It's not a joke anymore.
Out ofthe ideas you've come
up with, one ofthem flopped.
When you guys go after
girls like Jessi and Nancy,
it's my campaign
money that's being lost.
Which is the group that
supports John the least?
African Americans.
They don't like John.
- Boss those dark guys?
-As if you are fair and handsome.
- What kind of stu_ do they like?
- Music. Rap Music.
ln that case get a famous raper.
- Rapper.
- That's what l meant.
Get a few rappers
and make a show.
Let John Koy present it!
Then, just like the
politicians in our county,
he'll have to hug children with runny
noses, kiss old people, show some love,
and then dance
to the beat of their songs.
John is not interested in rap.
You have to act ifyou are politician.
Make him understand.
How will you organize this? How will
you get these people in?
ln Kerala, just some food
and liquor would work.
Here, it's beer and pi_a.
Seems like an expensive deal!
We lose money today. But
we sweep it up tomorrow.
Politics is an investment.
Two languages on this?
English and Spanish.
What's the percentage
of Spanish people here?
About 30 percent. But most
ofthem are illegal.
A good percentage ofthem
don't have voting rights.
Give me eveything.
Please buy me some black paint.
Proiect ''Language''.
No, no Spanish! Only English!
You're holding the
board upside down.
No, no Spanish! Only English!
Only English!
- Hey you wanna go for a ride?
- Go
- How much for you?
- Just go
Damn, you fine!
Yeah!
Let's increase the momentum.
Let's move it fast.
- What?
- l asked you to step it up a gear.
l almost forgot. What's the point in having
elections without fasting and lemon juice.
Proiect ''Hunger Strike''.
Jaganathan. Jaganathan
ln America the minimum age
for voting is 18 right?
So college students can vote.
Yes...
Do something. Announce that we will
waiver all education loans if we win.
Also give a beer allowance
to all students.
Proiect ''Youth''.
Free education today is key.
We want the young men oftoday to
study hard and become doctors...
..we want the young women to study hard and
become nurses and high powered secretaries.
And we want them
to have free beer.
Why? Well ifthey are wo_ing
so hard,
they deserve to relax
a little a_er wo_.
Political analyMrs view Jaganathan
as the new young prospect for Kerala.
Hello. No, no, no.
Sir is in a meeting with the
Mineral Beach Sand Miners.
Don't you undentand?
Call tomorrow.
Sir? Why are you
sitting like this?
Why are you still
drinking and not in bed?
l can't sleep now!
What's the time in America now?
Whatever time it is in America,
Jaganathan's time is now.
When l ask the time in America,
you don't have to talk about Jaganathan.
- Is it morning there now?
- Yes
ln that case l want a soda.
- Soda is right here.
- It's flat.
How can you tell by
just looking at it?
- It's not cold.
- Not cold?
- Did it burn you?
- It's freezing!
Not enough. l want it colder.
Go get me some cold soda.
He's angy at me because of
Jaganathan's success.
l've told him many times
not to treat me like this.
- Hello.
- Hello Sunny.
This is Francis Kuniappan.
Ah. What's new?
Don't listen to Jaganathan.
All his ideas are cheap.
Send him back.
There aren't too
many problems here now.
He's tying a lot of gimmicks.
Luckily, things are working out.
Why do you have him there
and take such a risk?
lfyou have him there, you
will face more problems.
l'm in the middle of
a big presentation.
l took the call just because it was you.
l'll call you as soon as this is over.
Hello. What l mean is....
Hello. Hello Sunny...
Soda.
When l asked for a cold soda...
l didn't mean soda
from the Himalayas.
This is arrogance. Don't
ty to be a smartass.
What ever cold l give you,
l get hot words in return.
- l know it's because you envy Jaganathan.
- What did you say now?
Did you say that you
know eveything?
Are you playing with me?
Jamie. Lookwho's here.
That's my son. Jamie.
Hello. Meet Jacks.
- l'll get you some wine. Yeah?
- Yes
- You're a football playe_
- Yeah!
Jamie!
Are you okay? Jamie!
Oh, little bird. Oh, lady love
You sing your beautiful
melody so_ly in my ears.
Young branches are searching
for fresh flowen again
Oh adorable breeze, you are
as beautiful as silk
Oh naughty breeM, as you caress my body
What can l do this moment?
What can l do?
Would you tell me?
What can l do? What can l do?
Would you tell me? What can l do?
Oh love, are you by my side?
Are you coming my way again?
Oh heart, are you by my side?
Or are you swinging to his side?
ls this magic?
Is this the season of flowen?
ls this the chill lightning, the breeM,
or the downpour of the moonlight?
ls this a dream?
Is this just a delusion?
ls this the rainbow that will vanish soon?
What can l do? What can l do?
Would you tell me? What can l do?
You're here without a coat?
What happened?
John. What brings you
here at midnight?
- l need to tell you something.
- Please come in.
We've got a problem.
And it's a big one.
OurJohn Koy was with a girl.
The video is out.
l see...
This hanky panky is a weakness
with politicians in all countries?
We've spent some money and
got most of the copies,
but the master copy is with George Hope.
He'll give it to the
media tomorrow morning.
Just when l think it's plain
sailing, there's a storm brewing.
l never thought this apple pie
was baked with hot chilli.
Please help me.
l've no choice but
to help you...
Ok...
Let's do the same we do in India.
Tell them it's all
computer graphics.
That won't
wo_ in America.
The media will stirthis thing up.
You sure there aren't
any other copies around?
Sure. A hundred percent sure.
Ok. l'll find a way.
What's your plan?
Let's keep it a surprise.
That way, there'll be
a kick when it all unfolds.
lNTERMISSlON
l can't wait to get to the room.
Don't do anything, Dracula!
Don't drink my blood!
Boss, is it you? Are you going to
a fancy dress competition tonight?
Proiect ''CIA''.
You mean CIAs?
No. Am...
Going...
Alone...
Where's the boss going?
Don't make a sound.
- Is he in the car?
- Not there!
The cafs shaking. Run!
Oh my God, Sex!
You iust don't get it, do you.
- It isn't moving even if l press
this thing. - Boss, put it in ''Drive''.
No need to teach him.
You just drive, Boss.
We,re o_!
Nice weather.
You put it in your mouth?
He did! Boss, he put
it in his mouth!
lt's getting serious guys.
l need back up. Over!
You know how hard it
is to get chewing tobacco?
The Police. Are you happy now?
They're following us.
Sirens and all!
- Boss, stop. We'll slip him a few
dollars and send him o_. - Shut up.
See there are a whole
Iot of other vehicles now.
There's a car behind.
Brake!
Drive faster, Boss. It's a big car!
Why're you driving so slowly?
No matter how big the car is, how
can l drive if we're out of gas?
No gas? See, the
yellow light is on!
Great! We're out of gas
in a serious car chase!
How can l be part of a serious car
chase with comedians like you?
l should've stayed a villain.
Boss, ifyou have a plastic bottle
l'll go get some gas.
You handle the car and the cops.
You know Sunny's number, right?
Boss.
Shop closed. Shop closed.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
l've seen you somewhere...
Where've we met before?
Are you Mr Jaganathan?
- How do you recogniM me?
- That's a silly question.
Are there people from Kerala
who don't know you?
You're all over
the newspapers.
But... why are you dressed like this?
l'll tell you later.
The cops are after me.
l need to get away.
- Cops?
- Yes.
You,ve come to the right place.
- l'll help you.
- Ok
But, there's a condition...
l want a picture with you.
l want to show it to my wife.
She likes you more than she likes me.
Ok.
l'm back.
Oh. Superman!
Yes...
Superman from Kerala.
l'm not Superman, l'm Badman!
Boss, it's me, Varkie.
- Do you recognize me?
- No...
This is Jabbar. We went into Keshavan
Nair's shop too; just like you did.
He likes you so much that he
gave us these costumes.
We came here to help you.
Why're you guys hassling me?
Not a sound. Come on.
Boss, why are we here?
Have we come here to steal?
Steal all the CDs and
DVDs from this house.
George has a secret
video of John.
- A secret video?
- Shhh!
You go this way. You go that way.
l'll go here.
Boss, it's you!
Go that way.
- Go there.
- There?
You go that way.
Don't come with me.
Let's get it before the boss comes.
- Be careful. - l hope l get to
see something juicy on the CD.
Careful.
You'll be electrocuted
ifyou touch it.
Careful.
A rat?!
Just a moment!
Gotta get rid of it now!
What the hell are you playing at?
- No problem. No problem.
- No problem?
Let me get rid of it.
Go down.
Almost there; a little more.
Brother! Watch out!
What,s going on?
Boss?
This is why l told you not
to watch Hollywood movies.
Boss!
These are iust designer lamps.
No laser security?
-All this hard work for nothing.
Here you go. - Thank you.
Boss, is it the secret video?
- Come down!
- l'm not coming.
- Ok. Sir, can you please join us?
- That's better. Show some respect.
- Don't make so much noise.
- l'm in pain!
Don't click, ,Play, yet!
My goodness!
Boss. He's notjust a governorwhen it
comes to such things. He's the President!
Wow!
Don't distract me.
Thank you Jaganathan. l really don't
know how to repay you for this.
Well! Thank me in Hindi.
You can say, ,Shukriya,.
My friend, this John
is a real stud.
Great pe_ormance!!!
A definite expert.
True. And what stamina!!!
You should've heard how they
wailed when l broke the CD.
Right! l had a real tantrum. l
wanted to watch it again.
Anyway, thank you so much guys.
- Our ratings have gone up.
- Really?
Please join us on
Friday if you're free.
We've a fund raising event for
the Indian American community.
Stunt raising?
- Fund.
- Oh. Fund. Fund.
The idea is to raise funds
for the election campaign.
There's fund raising here too?
- What else happens there?
- Food and drink,
and also John's speech.
God only knows how
much we'll raise.
Are you only going to
provide food and drink?
Why not ty something different?
l obviously can't have
dancing girls there!
No, it's clever. John's speech
is going to be boring, yes?
Are you serious?
l'm deadly serious!
lndians spend money
for mo things only:
God and Cinema.
How will l get hot dancers
at such short notice?
ls that a problem?
All married actresses from
Kerala settle here, right?
There's a saying, ''The
Iegs that danced, and
the mouth that sang,
can never be idle.''
Give it a ty. You can do it.
l am a hot lady for the local market...
l've been sold secretly.
Dear men, don't ty to cut in!
Don't look to breakthe
line and come with me!
Don't be adamant to get things done!
Come to me like thunder!
Do you have money? Do you have surprises?
If not, leave right now!
Are you full of life? Do you have energy?
l was enjoying myself
at the carnival when
someone winked at me and
gave me cotton candy.
l was enjoying myself
at the carnival when
someone winked at me and
gave me cotton candy.
l fell for it. Happiness filled me.
l le_ the town along with him.
He fell for me during the night.
He was full of love.
l forgot eveything else.
Shall we dance? Shall we sing?
If you don't want to, leave right now!
Do we have music here?
If not, leave right now.
My body is wrapped with
a green silk cloth.
Put some flowers on my bed.
My body is wrapped with
a green silk cloth.
Put some flowers on my bed.
Hey, don't leave without kissing me!
Don't drive me mad, naughty!
l've been a cystal for ages.
l get slippey by sight.
l get dirty if you touch me.
Do you have a wedding ring?
Do you have wedding garlands?
lf not, leave right now.
Do you have liquor?
Do you have beer?
lf not, leave right now.
Leave right now!
Do you have money?
Do you have surprises?
lf not, leave right now!
Shall we sing? Shall we dance?
If you don't want to, leave right now!
Do you have liquor? Do you have beer?
If not, leave right now!
Welcome to the Best
Politician awards.
What makes this award unique,
is that it is not political,
even though this is
an award for politicians.
lnstead this is a truly
merit based award.
This is an award chosen by the
public who voted by text message.
You're sure to get it
a_erthe dam issue.
And the award goes to...
l sent loads of texts myself.
- They'll announce it now.
- Our most favorite...
- MrJaganathan.
- Yes! Jaganathan!
As Jaganathan is abroad,
his close friend,
the King Maker,
Francis Kunjappan,
will collect the
award on his behalf.
To present the award may l welcome to the
stage,
Honorable Chief Minister Mr Thomas Joseph,
and from our sponson,
Oris, Mr Haafis.
Give them a big hand,
Iadies and gentlemen!
lsn't he done with these
fake accounts yet?
Sir, the president of the Party Youth Wing,
Joby Kuruvilla, is waiting outside.
He's a_er a seat at
the next election.
The Party Youth Wing
respects you a lot.
That's obvious; there are
only old men around here.
l'm the only one who
is young and active.
They will get
expiration from me.
- Inspiration.
- That's what l said. Call him.
Joby!
- Hi Joby. Come, sit.
- Hello, Sir.
lt's been ages since we met.
How are you?
l'm fine. Sir, you are
the youth's ummm...
- inspiration?
- Yes. That's right.
- He's no genius either.
- Sir...
lt is due to your e_orts that
Jaganathan's reached such a high position.
Sir, you're our role model.
You're our pam's King Maker.
Could you possibly push my
case towards high office too?
Joby, don't wory about it.
l'll take care of it. Ok?
He'll push you. He'll push you.
Kuniappan is going to help me out.
Stupid application!
l am fed up with these guys.
Welcome.
l'll take care of it.
l'll take care ofJoby's case.
ldiot. l can't even help
myself here.
Let's go.
This is like digging
your own grave.
Evey newspaper is
talking about him.
Calm down.
l've spent a lot of money
getting you this post.
You'll get back double
what you spent.
He's not grown big enough
to take my job from me.
No, no, no. Don't
underestimate him.
When he comes back
from America,
he is going to get a King's welcome here.
Wait and see.
King's welcome? Nonsense!
Now, we have reached the
Iast phase ofthe campaign.
A_erthis l can finally
sleep peacefully.
But these next few days are
the most important for us.
- Debates. - Debate?
- Which means?
George and John will get an
opportunity to formally debate
their manifestos and plans for
California on the same stage.
There'll be live TV coverage.
lt's make or break for
both candidates.
Why do theAmericans
complicate things?
Why do they put
themselves through this,
just to get in and steal
from the public purse.
Even if it's for stealing, the
politicians here accept it.
He's going to talk
gibberish on stage.
He'd be fine if it was
all about women.
But will he be able
to handle a rebate?
- It's not a ''rebate''. It's a ''debate''.
No worries. l have good writers who can
write first class political speeches.
We'll make them write
a kickass speech.
Why do we have to sweat it
when we have Holl_ood,
the industy that charms
the world with cinema.
We can get a good scriptwriter to write
an inspirational speech for John Koy.
ln that case, will we get the
writer ofJurassic Park?
An awesome speech that
Iasts for ten minutes.
Fireworks written in English.
He'll get a standing ovation, even
though people won't understand a thing.
People will fall
for his speech.
lf it were in Kerala,
we'd know who to get.
Yes! l know someone too.
l get it. We'll do it.
lfwe win this debate, your campaign
here will be successfully completed.
- Dude! American style.
- Yes!
- l'll transfer the money, Jagan.
- That's great.
But help me with the
selection of writers, too.
Help him, Boss.
Ok, done!
That's a lot.
- It's just my second.
- Not that...
Jaganathan's fan page
is flooded with 'Likes'.
Can we steal some
and make them ours?
lt's Facebook, not politics.
We can'tjust steal people.
- They'll come to us only ifthey want.
- Make them ''Like'' us. - How?
Bribe them with
cury and alcohol!
Sir, this isn't a rally where we can pull
in a crowd with free food and drink.
Youngsten will hit 'Like' only
if they feel like doing it.
How does this work? Please
help me understand.
You get online through a
cell phone or computer,
and then type www.facebook.com.
A page will open.
You use your name and email to create
a profile. That's your account.
You can upload your pictures
and update your status there.
When you do such things, people will
comment, like, and share your posts.
You can also talk about things
on Twitter like Shakira does
and loads of people
will ''Follow'' you.
You can also ''Poke'' ifyou want.
That's it. Do you understand?
What did you understand?
l understood that people like
me will never understand this.
This is like explaining
electricity to a cat...
Rohit's coming here next week
from central government.
Clean up the roads and put some tar
at least on the bits he'll drive on.
Or else, he'll take yourjob
with him on his way back to Delhi.
[in Hindi] Hello Mr. Rohit.
[in Hindi] We welcome
you to Kerala.
[in Hindi] How was your Germany?
lt's ''journey''.
Journey. Journey. Journey.
Why this annoying Hindi?
ls it so difficult to ask if
his journey was good in Hindi?
Unlike ours, Hindi is
not an easy language.
lf l don't impress him in Hindi, l'll
be out ifthere's a problem from Delhi.
That's why l'm
struggling so much.
[in Hindi] Hello Mr. Rohit.
[in Hindi] We welcome
you to Kerala.
Please come. Please come.
Let's get in there.
[in Hindi] Hello Mr. Rohit. We
welcome you to Kerala.
Where's the garland?
Long live Rohit!
There's a small problem.
What is it?
The usual route is out. There are
billboards ofJaganathan along the road.
But no worries. l've
changed the route.
That's enough.
Filling in potholes for
10 km all for nothing!
But it's ok as long as
his photo isn't seen.
- How's the new route?
- Full of potholes.
Tell the driver not
to hit any big ones.
We don't want the same problems we had when
the minister came from Delhi last time...
Eveyone's gone. Come.
Out the way!
Move please!
Sir, you sit with him.
l'll sit in the front.
The Chief Minister is in
the back with him. Move!
l'll go in the policeieep.
Hello.
[in Hindi] Hello... Yes Mummy...
[in Hindi] Yes Mummy...
[in Hindi] l'veiust reached Cochin.
[in Hindi] Yes. l've had my milk.
[in Hindi] Yes, yes, yes.
Say something in Hindi.
Me?
[in Hindi] These days,
the heat is too much.
- [in Hindi] What?
- It's hot. It's hot.
Pothole!
- Can you please avoid the open mine sha_s?
- l didn't learn to drive at the circus.
This is like driving
in a wall of death!
lfwe miss by an
inch, we're in hell.
Once he's gone, l'm going
be driving you, Sonny boy!
[in Hindi] See. See. Coconut tree.
Coconut tree. That side! That side!
[in Hindi] Mr Rohit,
it's vey beautiful.
Kerala is proud ofJaganathan, who is
experimenting
with the democratic process in America.
Go sit there. Always
in front ofthe TV.
Please come in, come in.
Hello.
Please sit.
[in Hindi] Vey hot. Vey hot.
Thank you. So who is
this Chacko Nathan?
There you go...
Trouble comes in the form of a magazine.
What?
Where're you going
smelling like that?
l...
going out for a...
romantic dinner with my...
sweetheart Jessi...
Any problem?
Yes. l have a problem.
Question: You always say that
Indians are your brothen and sisten,
so what happened to that?
- Dear little Varkie.
- Don't call me that.
When you see trees,
l see the sky.
- Understand?
- No.
Her heart. l check.
At heart Indian.
But she, American citizen.
Whatever. My stomach's rumbling
like cray l'm so hungy.
Let's get ready and
go with the boss.
You don't have to follow me eveywhere
like a couple of stray dogs.
Don't you wish to see me
get married and have kids?
- We'll see.
- No need.
- Hello.
- Hi, Jacks.
- Where are we going? - We're going
to a Mediterranean restaurant.
l hope you like
Mediterranean food.
l like Pomeranian too.
Pomeranian?
- Jacks you are too funny.
- Yeah, Yeah, Yeah.
Let's go.
- Thank you.
We'll have a drink?
You want to have a Merlot?
- You don't like Merlot?
- Marilyn Monroe?
Jacks you are vey funny
and you know that.
Sory. One minute...
toilet and...
- Ok.
l think there's a problem.
l'll have to take someone with me
to understand what she's saying.
What was that? Mediterranean... Merlot...
l am confused by all this.
Merlot is a red wine that's
made from special grapes.
Why can't sheiust call it wine?
When you order Mediterranean
food, ask for hummus.
lt's chickpeas. Just call it ''hummus''.
Just to show that you know.
What's that? Hummers?
Not ''hummen'', ''hummus''.
Boss...
What are you doing there?
We'rejust having fun with
these princesses here.
Let John Koy pick
up the tab forthis!
Don't make John Koy sory!
No, No, No. Shall we
take them to Kerala?
Hummus. Merlot.
Merlot. Hummus.
Sory.
Here's the wine for you.
- Is eveything ok?
- Yeah ok.
What do you want to have?
- Hummus?
You like hummus? Even l like hummus.
With pita bread?
Yeah. Yeah.
Jacks, before ordering...
l have to tell you something
and it is vey important.
Your eyes. So beautiful.
Thank you.
Jacks. Actually...
Your nose. So, so beautiful.
Thanks.
- Jacks can l say something?
- Your lips...
So, so, so beautiful.
l am not going any further down.
Jacks, now can l speak?
Actually...
My mother, she says not talking
while eating. Bad for health.
- Mother?
- Yeah.
Oh, Merlot!
Nice! Good!
Jacks, we need to go from here.
- We need to go from here right now.
- Where?
- Jacks get up. - What?
- Let's go from here.
Let's go.
Jacks, run!
What's this? What do you want?
- Hey!
- Leave me alone!
- Let go of me!
- Hey, leave her alone!
Hey! No!
Suit. Not comfortable.
This dhoti. Vey comfortable.
Come on.
Game Over!
l told you about
my husband right?
He was into gambling.
Jessi's husband was
a gambling addict.
He gambled with
all the money he got.
When he lost all his own
and his family's money,
he started borrowing money
from a local thug, Tony Zebrano.
ln the end, when the debts
started rising, he ran away.
Poor girl.
Jamie. Mommy's home.
Where are you Jamie. l'll
just check upstain.
Tara...
Jamie... Are you guys there?
Hey!
- Jessi...
- Boss...
Hey!
What happened?
Where's Jamie?
What happened? Get some water.
You release the money tomorrow. l
release the kid. Police bad idea.
lt's Tony's message. He's got Jamie.
He's demanding money.
They'll kill Jamie.
Relax. Relax. Nothing will happen to Jamie.
l promise, ok.
Nothing will happen
to Jamie, ok?
No, no, no.
l promise you, ok?
We can't let this happen.
Let's go fix it.
No. Don't go. They'll kill Jamie.
Don't go.
Ok, ok. You call Tony.
You call Tony.
Hello.
Hello? Tony?
Tony?
One million dollars.
Tomorrow night.
Ok?
But no bad things to the child.
Bad things to the child. You remember?
That American flag? Dhoti? Flag?
American flag. Dhoti. Ok?
You remember.
No bad things to the child.
Ok.
Get Sunny on the line. He hasn't
called us since the campaign ended.
- Relax
- Jacks, l'm scared
Hi, this is Sunny. Please leave a
message and l'll call you back.
Voice mail. It's been like this since
yesterday. He hasn't called back yet.
Can we go check?
- Yes.
- Come on. Ok.
Relax. l'll call you.
l'll call you, ok. Relax.
- Jaganathan?
- Not forgotten my name then?
l called you mice.
l was busy with the accounts.
Come in. l wanted to
talk to you anyway.
Can you guys wait here please?
- l have no secrets from them.
- No, it's not that.
l want to talkto
you personally.
Guys, ifyou don't mind please.
Boss, you go. We'll wait here.
Ok.
- Can l offer you a drink?
- No thanks.
Now that the campaign is over, we
are planning to go back to Kerala.
Sure. l booked your tickets.
There is a small change
regarding the funds.
lnstead oftransferring
all the funds to Kerala,
l want one million
here right away.
There's a small problem
with the funds Jaganathan.
Luckily, your mad
ideas did work for us.
But, that doesn't mean
l should give so much
to a worthless
politician from Kerala.
l've also spent loads for all the crap
you and your goons got up to here,
not to mention the expenses
you guys racked up!
How can you say that?
l've completed the job
you asked me to do.
Ok. l'll speak
to John ifyou like.
l'll call him foryou...
l have good news and
bad news for you, John.
Well... Tell me the good news and
keep the bad news to younelf.
Our ratings are up.
But we have exceeded on
the budget drastically.
Winning is OUR responsibility.
Money is YOUR responsibility.
Not mine.
l know that John. But we need to
pay Jaganathan for his services.
l really need your help.
l am going to bethe next
governor ofCalifornia.
Do we really need
to pay that guy?
l mean... campaign's over.
Pick up your drink.
Welcome to politics.
Even though your work is
done with this campaign,
my political career is
just starting here.
lf l want them to consider me for
a cabinet post in the future
it's my responsibility to keep this
election campaign cost e_ective.
This money is vey
important for Jessi.
l promised that l'd
get back to herwith it.
Jessi?
How many such Jessis do you want.
l'll arrange a thousand ofthem for you.
Promises might be nothing
to you, but for me...
lt's not only Jessi who's
waiting forthe money,
it's also the future of many talented
sports men and women in India.
Don't get sentimental now.
Go back to Kerala.
Play some old politics and
Iook to earn some money.
Take Jessi with you too
ifyou want.
lt won't be di_icult to make
money if she's with you.
Don't make me swear with the same
tongue that once called you, ''Sir''.
l'm asking for
the last time,
areyougivingme
themoneyornot?
Are you tying to scare me?
This is a di_erent county.
l iust have to make one call,
and you'll be behind bars for the
rest ofyour life. Damn dog!
What did you call me? A dog?
You really don't know
what l'm capable of.
l am not a dog.
l'm a bandicoot!
A bandicoot digging through
your grave without you knowing.
Do you know something?
l've always thought ofyou
you as a bit of a comedian.
Sunny. You are wrong there.
You ask the people of Kerala.
l am not a comedian.
l'm a hero who also knows
how to play comedy.
l made an entire county laugh.
But, now you've made me cy.
You definitely make a good villain
Thanks for the compliment.
But, l can take care ofthings
here myselffrom now on.
You can go now.
Lord Shiva has a third
eye on his forehead.
But this Jaganathan
has eyes all over.
Keep that in mind.
- What happened?
- What happened, Boss?
Jessi, come to
Univenal Studios.
What happened?
We have a lot ofworkto do
before tomorrow evening.
l'll meet you in
the hotel lobby.
- Do we need to come?
- No.
You start packing.
l have to do this myself.
This bandicoot's game is
just about to start.
l don't think there's
any point waiting.
- Shall we call the police?
- l think we should.
- Do you know the numbe_
- Yes, 911 .
Shall l call?
ls it ringing?
The cafs outside. l'll pack
and be back in 10 minutes.
- Where were you?
- l'm a bandicoot...
and you never know when l'll
arrive or when l'll leave.
- What's he saying?
- No idea.
l'm going to really miss you.
l miss double.
Boss...
Give her a French kiss.
lndian kiss is enough.
Good morning California.
Today is election day!
Election day! Election day!
The exit polls are
favoring John Koy.
But, there's still hope
for George Hope.
The Koy campaign was
celebrating last night
with the latest polls showing their
ratings going through the roof.
The first exit polls are being announced
here, and there are shocks in store.
Going against recent opinion polls
that showed Koy well in the lead
exit polls from voters showed both
parties hanging neck and neck
it's too close to call who will win.
Just in. Democrat George
Hope wins the election.
George Hope is the next
governor of California!
ln a resounding victoy.
Hope secured 670/o ofthe vote
with John Koy trailing
back with just 330/o .
Congratulations foryour loss.
Mr Sunny Kurishingal.
What cheap trick did you play?
l told you...
lf l know how to help you
climb up the ladder...
l know exactly how to
bring you down too.
- You damn traitor....
- Don't raise your voice.
Don't you want to know where
your misfortune came from?
- Jagan, l didn't expect Sunny to
play a game like this. - Me neither.
And he won't expect me to
play a game like this.
No time to waste. Have you
got the thing l asked for?
Here...
- Her problem first.
- Here.
The balance a_er our success.
Mr Pe_ect Andy turned out
to be a real politician.
lf the campaign didn't
go as expected...
l had a trump card
to make John win.
Meet Mr Dupe Lee.
Hello, Mr Hope.
This is the voting
machine designed by Lee.
Even though it looks original.
It's a duplicate.
ltjust needs some simple
re-programming,
no matter how many
votes in the ballot.
This is how it wo_s.
lfJohn gets ten votes, only one
vote will be registered to him.
The remaining nine
will go to George.
Sir, a ten... Sachidananda
please explain...
No need to explain.
l understood eveything.
This is a true politician. One who
understands fraud in any language.
Jack, how are you going to replace the
originals with the duplicates?
- Jacks.
- Hey how is Jamie?
- He's okay. Let's go.
- Come.
As planned, we waited with the duplicate
machines in a duplicate truck with Dupe Lee.
Eveything was duplicate.
The money that you
cheated me out of...
Well, l used the same
money against you.
Proiect ''Bribey''.
The police here don't have pot bellies,
like they do in our county.
That's the only
di_erence bemeen them.
There's no place on
earth without an Indian.
But, ifthere were, you'd surely
find a Chinese guy there.
Victorwas a Chinese man in the
California election committee.
Dupe Lee's close friend.
- Dupe Lee...
- Thanks buddy!
Just by changing the number
plates on the trucks,
a never-seen-before honest
election started in California.
What about the truck?
Do you want it, Andy?
Run!
This is not the time
for sentiment.
Run baby, run!
The next governor, George
Hope, will make sure
the news ofthe bomb and
the truck doesn't come out.
After all, his political
consultant is me: The Bandicoot!
l will expose all your
tricks in the media.
The elections are over. Who is
going to believe all this now?
People will just say that it is
the frustration of a failure.
Moreover, Governor George Hope is
ready to do whatever l say.
So, l've sent John's
old sex video to him.
l actually broke the original.
But our Jabbar was such a
fan of John's pe_ormance,
that he made a copy ofthe CD.
The pervert!
- Dog! This won't end here!
- Hey...
Don't get violent.
Turn on the TV
and take a look.
Watch the rest of
the action there.
J Sports Academy, which
will give Kerala sports
an international face, is all
set for inauguration.
J Sports Academy will open doors
for the younger generation in sports.
Eveyone was excited to learn who
would inaugurate the academy.
lt will be inaugurated by
the wife of V.P Sathyan,
the Indian footballer
who tragically took his own life.
The Boss is inside.
l'll call him now.
- Look who's here.
- Hey, Jaganathan.
- Flowers from the State of California.
- Thank you, Andy.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Good morning.
l've always seen
you as a competitor.
l lost the game
l played againstyou.
But l'm not upset,
after all, l've lost playing
against a champion.
Don't stop with one.
Take about four or five.
But when you update this on
Facebook, please tag me too.
Nowadays, we need
Facebook for eveything!
l want to tell you something.
Please don't say, ''No.''
l have accepted an
assignment from Pakistan.
Elections are coming there.
You have to go.
You haven't changed,
have you, Mr Kunjappan?
Sir, go and sit there.
He didn't fall for that.
Hello.
Yes.
- Jagan
- Jaganathan?
Yes, yes, yes.
Boss. Call from Jamaica.
Babe, l swear she's
just a friend.
My God. How will l
make her understand?
Let me explain.
l'm getting another call.
One moment.
- Hello.- Hi my name is Maria.
l'm calling from Brazil.
We heard a lot about you.
- We're wondering if it's possible...
- You want Boss?
Okay, okay, okay. Boss.
Hello...
England?
Election?
- Can you hold? He's busy.
- Oh no, no.
Going for honeymoon.
Honeymoon.
You change the
election for one...
forthree months.
End Beep